TSUKUYOMI
DON'T WASTE THEM BY DRINKING THEM ON THEIR OWN.
WHACK
MATH: A
MUSIC: A
PE: A
CLASSICS: A
YACHIYO
YACHIYO RUNAMI HOLDS BIGGEST EVER VR CONCERT, FANS ARE IN TEARS
IROHA SAKAYORI
100 MILLION GLOBAL USERS!
TSUKUYOMI'S AI CREATOR, YACHIYO
YACHIYO RUNAMI
BANG
BANG BANG
HOW TO INSTANTLY STOP BABIES CRYING
BABY & KIDS' CLOTHES NISHITAKEYA
PAYMENT COMPLETE
STREET INTERVIEWS: A MAN IN HIS 30S
GROWL
IROHA'S REVOLUTIONARY CHEAP MEAL PANCAKES
MADE WITH FLOUR AND WATER
CAREER PATH PREFERENCE SURVEY FORM
1. PLAN FOR HIGHER EDUCATION
2. PREFERRED UNIVERSITY
WALLET BALANCE ¥452
COMPARED TO PREVIOUS DAY -¥124400
SUPERMARKET MISONO ¥1,090
SUPERMARKET MISONO ¥540
KONDO MEAT ¥1,239
SAKAMOTO FISH ¥2,680
BISTRO MATSUO ¥2,000...
GULP
GASP
EEK!
ALARM
SNOOZE
SORRY IT'S NOT CHARMING...
YACHIYO RUNAMI
TSUKUYOMI COAST MINI CONCERT
JULY 18, 2030 21:00
IROHA SAKAYORI
BLACK ONYX
FIRST STREAMING SESSION
HELLO FROM THE MOON! IT'S KAGUYA!
MAKE LOTS OF FUJU, STUDY COOKING, DO CONCERTS. TO WIN THE YACHIYO CUP: GET PEOPLE TO WATCH OUR STREAMS
KAGUYA 8910TH PLACE
FAN COUNT: 14, TOTAL FUJU: 232
LIVE WATCH "TOMORROW WITHOUT SHADOWS"
DON'T UPLOAD IT
CURRENT RANK 1: BLACK ONYX
DISTANCE: 12.55M
NEUTRALIZED SUCCESS!
THIS STREAM HAS ENDED
KAGUYA 464TH PLACE
FANS: 114,137, TOTAL FUJU: 282,991
I LIKE MYSELF
KAGUYA
KAGUYA 280TH PLACE
FANS: 193,621, TOTAL FUJU: 631,405
I LIKE MYSELF
KAGUYA
KAGUYA & IRO P CHANNEL
Q3: IF YOU COULD BRING ONE THING TO A DESERTED ISLAND, WHAT WOULD IT BE?
A: IRO-P
IROHA'S BUSY, SO TEACH ME THE GAME
ROKA: SURE THING
MAMI: OKAY!
BEAUTY INFLUENCER ROKA
170,000 FANS
FOOD INFLUENCER MAMI
120,000 FANS
VICTORY
FIRST TIME PLAYING KASSEN!
THAT'S WHAT I LIKE ABOUT YOU!
I LOVE THAT YOU'RE A LITTLE TROUBLEMAKER
BATTLE FOR KAGUYA: KASSEN TOURNAMENT
PREPARING FOR STREAM
PLEASE SUBSCRIBE!
LUXURY HIGH-RISE CONDO EXPERIENCE
3 BEDROOMS 350,000 YEN
UNREAD MESSAGE: SATOSHI TAKEI (MANAGER)
WHAT A CUTE LITTLE SISTER. GET PLENTY OF REST
OTAKO THE LOYAL DOG
YACHIYO CUP MIDWAY REPORT
#9 RYOGEN KOKI, #8 AL-MARI PEARL
#7 UNDOJI SUIMA, #6 RANDOM OMEGA
#5 KAMIKITA RINGO #4 KUROBA KAKA
#3 NUKUMI YUKUMO
HIS LAID BACK VOICE IS SO SOOTHING!
#2 TERERIRI TIETATE
#1 BLACK ONYX
LADY KAGUYA
AUGUST 23RD
MESSAGE FROM AKIRA MIKADO TO KAGUYA
I'M AKIRA MIKADO FROM BLACK ONYX.
CONGRATS ON REACHING A MILLION FANS!
HOW ABOUT A BATTLE BETWEEN ME AND YOU?
LOSE AND YOU MARRY ME.
WIN AND I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
#43 KAGUYA & IRO P
TSUKUYOMI
YACHIYO CUP RESULTS ANNOUNCEMENT
NONINANA PANCAKES ¥278
LUXURY PANCAKE MIX ¥402
PANCAKE MIX SUPER CHEWY ¥329
IROHA'S ROOM
UNTITLED.WAV
UPDATED 2020/01/2
29TH: SUMMER CLASS, PART-TIME JOB
30TH: CONCERT, PRACTICE TEST
31ST: PART-TIME JOB, SUMMER CLASS
LARGE-SCALE COMMUNICATION FAILURE
IN TACHIKAWA CITY, TOKYO, REASON UNKNOWN
MOM: 1 HOUR AGO, 10 MISSED CALLS
SUMMER CLASSES COMMON TEST:
JAPANESE MODERN CLASSICAL LITERATURE
PRINCESS KAGUYA RETURNS TO THE MOON
9/1 (SUN) FIREWORKS FESTIVAL
8 MIN WALK FROM STATION
GIVING YOU BACK WHAT I'VE SPENT. SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE!
SENDING
FAILED
SO ANNOYING
10 YEARS LATER
COSMIC PRINCESS KAGUYA!