You didn't trust me, so you followed me?
Then what did I just see?
Your mom looks totally fine.
Mom, mom, enough!
Mom, the baby is gone.
I'm sorry I didn't trust you.
Have you seen Tulip? She's in danger!
I'll help look for her too.
I'm dating Tulip now.
I did everything you told me to.
Now it's time you gave me my reward.
[Two months ago]
- Khaw.
- Yeah?
I think I'm in love with you.
Yeah.
That's it? That's all you've got?
What?
Thank you.
How long do I have to wait?
Wait for what?
For the day I actually get to be with you.
Do you know why I wanted to study here?
No.
You said it had to be this place.
So I followed you. That's it.
There's someone here I wanted to find.
And I knew they'd definitely study here.
Don't tell me you already liked someone.
And you followed them here.
Then what am I to you?
No.
She's a girl.
A girl?
And it's the complete opposite of "like".
What's that supposed to mean?
Do you really love me?
Can you do me a favor?
Like what?
Go flirt with this girl for me.
Make sure she falls for you.
Desperately in love with you.
Then you dump her.
I want her to understand
what losing someone she loves feels like.
What for?
I can't tell you yet.
But if you do it...
I...
willl be yours. Forever.
I've done everything you told me to.
You told me to go flirt with Tulip.
Make her like me.
What are you doing all this for?
I still can't tell you yet.
So...
How long do I have to pretend I like Tulip?
Until...
Until she really falls for you. Hard.
Like, really hard.
And when that time comes...
you dump her.
Just so you know, everything I'm doing,
it's all for you.
[Wawwa - 2 missed calls]
Hey.
Did the noise wake you up?
No, no.
Why did you get home just now?
Oh. My mom wasn't feeling well last night.
So I kept her company last night.
Is she better now?
Yeah. She's fine now.
I've got a morning class.
I'll go shower first.
Hey, wait.
I don't know if you saw my message.
The one where I said I'm dating Tao now.
Oh, yeah?
He finally found the guts to ask you?
Yeah, I was kinda surprised too.
But now that we're actually together
I don't really know how to act.
Don't overthink it.
He's a good guy.
And I believe he can take care of you.
I hope so too.
And whose shirt are you wearing?
It's huge, like a guy's shirt.
It's mine.
I like wearing oversized shirts.
You didn't know?
Hey.
Tulip.
- Tao, sir!
- What?
Is this your grand opening or what?
Hey, hey! Keep walking. Stop teasing.
Holding hands already.
They're asking for it.
Tulip.
When class is over, come find me.
What's up?
I've got something to talk to you about.
Just the two of us.
What happened?
Well... last night...
Wawwa! Wawwa!
Did you file a police report yet?
Not yet.
The Professor said
they don't want this blowing up.
Someone literally got attacked.
How is that not a big deal?
I'm also waiting for Wawwa
to wake up and fill me in.
So... why were you calling Wawwa last night?
Last night, Wawwa was looking for you.
She had something
she wanted to talk to you about.
So I helped her try to find you.
Oh... those missed calls yesterday?
Sorry. I was with Tao,
so I didn't get to call back.
It's okay.
Wawwa just found out something.
So she wanted to talk to you.
About what?
Baikhaw.
Wawwa said Baikhaw once poisoned a senior
at her old school.
The girl almost died.
What?
If that's really true,
it means you're living with someone who's...
seriously dangerous.
How can you say
that I'm blowing this out of proportion?
My daughter almost died!
Isn't that big enough for you?
Ma'am. Is something wrong?
Tulip, this professor won't let me
file a report
because they're afraid
it'll hurt the university's reputation.
That's not the reason.
We haven't gone to the police
because at the campus,
not a single CCTV camera
caught what happened.
None of them?
Yes.
Right now, we don't even know for sure
that this incident actually
happened the way it seems.
What do you mean by that?
Are you saying that Wawwa made this up
and injured herself this badly on purpose?
Here, this is Wawwa's bag.
It was found at the scene.
Wawwa.
It's me, Tulip.
Tulip! Why can't I see anything?
- What happened to me?
- Calm down, okay?
You probably won't be able to see
for a little while.
And... is... is anyone else here?
No, no. Right now, it's just you and me.
Tulip, it was so really scary.
Someone... I don't know who...
Poured some kind of chemical
right onto my eyes.
It burned so much.
And did you see their face at all?
Who was it?
No, nothing. It was so dark.
I...
I think it had to be Baikhaw.
Tulip, I found out
that Baikhaw poisoned a senior
at her old school.
It has to be her.
She must've known I found out.
So she came after me and attacked me.
Wawwa.
Let me ask you honestly.
Were you using drugs?
Huh?
What did you just say?
It's just...
The professor found this in the bathroom.
What is it?
Tulip.
I don't even know what that is.
But if it's drugs, they're not mine.
You know I don't do drugs.
But it was in your bag.
It's not mine!
Anyone could've put it there.
Tulip. You have to believe me.
Baikhaw... she must've planted it in my bag.
Wawwa. Enough!
This isn't something small anymore.
But it's not mine!
I have no idea how it got in my bag.
- Someone's framing me.
- Wawwa.
- Mom? Mom! Help me!
- Dear...
The drugs aren't mine.
- I'm here, sweetheart.
- Mom, please help me.
Someone attacked me
and planted drugs on me.
It wasn't me.
What's this?
Chamomile tea.
It helps you sleep.
Thanks.
About Wawwa, don't stress over it.
She brought this on herself.
Yeah...
I just can't stop thinking about it.
What kind of friend am I?
How did I not know she was like this?
Why didn't anything feel off to me?
Hey. You haven't been close for ages.
It's normal.
People grow apart.
You end up knowing them less.
Haven't you heard?
The older you get, the smaller your circle.
I know, but... I just feel guilty.
I couldn't help her at all.
Just the fact that you care...
makes you a damn good friend already.
Just help her as much as you can.
Yeah...
But people have their own problems
they need to deal with themselves.
Even you do.
Drink your tea, and get some sleep.
Thanks.
I'm out of my anxiety meds.
Guess I'll have to go home and get them.
I really don't want to go home.
I don't want to see my parents.
If you don't wanna go, then don't.
But I'm out of meds.
Honestly, I could just make this tea
for you every day,
and you'd sleep fine.
Seriously,
you go home, they say shitty things to you,
and you come back here all upset.
Total waste of your time.
I don't want to go back either.
In that house... well...
no one understands me.
Pick up the phone. We need to talk.
Have you seen this? Season one was insane.
I'm like a hardcore fan.
I watched it ages ago.
I barely remember anything.
No worries.
You can ask me if you have any questions.
Popcorn.
Let me feed you. There you go.
Tao.
What's wrong, Tulip?
It's just... I...
If you're nervous, it's okay.
I brought protection.
No, I just feel like... this is too soon.
Too soon? Tulip. How is it too soon?
We've been feeling the same way, haven't we?
You like me too, don't you?
I do, but...
Let's not rush.
Tao!
It's fine. Whatever.
So you don't like him or what?
I do like him.
Then why won't you just let him...
Why won't you let him sleep with you?
I just feel like it's a bit too fast.
Oh, come on!
What era are you living in?
You're not even that young.
It's not too fast.
I'm not old-fashioned or anything, but...
I just want a bit more time.
If you're scared,
I can go with you to buy condoms, okay?
It's not that.
So why are you overthinking everything?
I just don't want you
to end up fighting with him over this.
- I've been watching you two...
- Whatever. Forget it.
Anyway, what about the faculty party tonight?
Can't ditch, can I?
Probably not. It's a big event.
Okay. I have to go.
- Please take care of the bill for me.
- Yeah, see you.
Scan, please.
All set.
[Mom]
It's not even 9 PM yet.
What's the rush?
Drink fast, get drunk fast,
then go home fast.
Yes, ma'am, queen introvert.
I'm gonna go top up my drink.
Can I get a refill, please?
Tulip.
About yesterday, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
I should've waited
until you were really ready.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I get it.
Don't pressure yourself, Tulip.
I'll wait until you're really ready.
Okay.
Hey, what are you doing?
What's got you so stressed?
I just don't wanna overthink stuff.
What's going on?
Can you tell me?
Namo, have you ever had a girlfriend?
Why?
Just wondering about something.
But never mind. Forget it.
Huh?
Are you teasing me?
Now I wanna know even more.
That makes me want to tell you even less.
Never mind, girl stuff.
Namo.
Can you help carry the stuff in the back?
All done.
Anything else you need?
No.
You know, right?
Tao and Tulip are dating now.
Yeah, I know.
Okay. Good.
But you like Tulip, don't you?
Right?
So I want you to leave her alone.
I don't want any trouble.
Hey!
I just want to be her friend.
I'm not trying to cause problems.
No.
I don't want Tao and Tulip fighting
because of you.
I haven't even done anything.
I'm just worried about Tulip.
Good.
Thanks for caring.
But I think Tulip has me as her friend,
and Tao as her boyfriend.
That's enough.
Anything else is unnecessary.
Why aren't you singing?
I'm tired.
Not having fun?
I am, but I drank too much. I'm drunk.
Same. I'm drunk too.
- Hey.
- Well, well, well.
- So sweet, you two.
- Can we steal you away
from your sweetheart for a sec, Tulip?
Go sing for us.
Please?
No, I don't want to.
Just a little bit!
Come on. Sing for us.
I wanna hear that pretty voice.
I'm tired of hearing this one sing.
Please?
No, I'm drunk already.
Hey, guys! Anyone wanna hear Tulip sing?
Let me hear you!
Tulip! Tulip! Tulip!
Sing with me!
Cheers!
Give her a big hand!
- That was amazing!
- So good. So, so good.
Can I toast with the singer?
Cheers!
Half a glass.
- Half!?
- For you, yeah.
Your voice is seriously beautiful.
If my friend sang, it'd be amazing too.
Amazingly bad.
Also a faculty Princess.
Dang!
They want to clink your glass.
You trying to get me drunk?
Come on, come on, yeah!
Half a glass.
What's wrong now?
Tulip told me
that you tried to sleep with her.
And what about it?
Did you really need to go that far?
Aren't you the one who told me to do it?
Yeah, but...
- What, are you jealous?
- No, I'm not jealous.
Then what's your problem?
You act like if I actually fell for Tulip,
you'd suddenly date me for real.
- You idiot, you're drunk.
- Drunk, my ass.
Tao!
People will see. Stop.
Fine.
I'll just go screw Tulip
and get this over with.
Then this shitty deal between us
can finally end.
Come on, step by step.
- Easy, careful.
- Where are we going?
Everyone's gone home already.
I don't wanna go home yet.
Well, you're already home, so...
She smells so bad.
Oh damn, don't cover her. She reeks.
Do you wanna shower?
Is she up for it?
You know what? I love you two the most.
- Yeah, yeah.
- One of you is my boyfriend.
And the other is my best friend.
I'll let you sleep, Tulip. I'll head out now.
Oh, Namo.
Don't be mad. I love you too.
Don't need to get all touchy.
I'm not offended.
You're an important friend to me.
I care about you too.
And I won't let anyone hurt you.
Thank you.
I love you guys so much.
I love you all.
Namo, you go and head back first.
I'll stay and keep an eye on Tulip for a bit.
Baikhaw's here too.
Yeah, I know, but...
In case Tulip wakes up
while Baikhaw's asleep or something.
Just go ahead, okay?
I'll head back on my own later.
Okay.
- See you.
- Yeah.
Besides my mom,
you're the only one who's ever bathed me.
How could I not?
You smelled like puke. So bad.
Thank you for everything.
You're so damn good to me.
You're like the big sister
I've always wanted.
Sometimes I think that too.
Hey...
About Tao...
I think I'm okay now.
About what?
Like...
I'm ready to move forward with him.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I'm okay now.
I feel like I'm falling more and more
in love with him.
My head hurts.
Is Tulip asleep?
Yeah.
What are you waiting for?
We're not done talking.
So tell me.
What exactly do you want me to do with Tulip?
Just keep doing what you've been doing.
Even if I sleep with her,
you don't feel anything?
Do you even have any feelings for me at all?
What are you talking about?
I've done all this for you,
and you still can't give me an answer?
Sometimes you act like
you don't care about me.
And sometimes you act like
you don't want me to move on.
Are you keeping me around because
all you want is to sleep with me?
I don't want to talk about this.
Or you're keeping me around just to use me.
No matter how much I do for you,
you'll never see me as anything more.
- Are you drunk or what?
- I'm not drunk.
I think about this all the time.
I just never said it.
Baikhaw.
I'm done letting you use me.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Baikhaw...
Baikhaw!
Why are you sleeping out here?
Why is the room such a mess?
I'm drunk as hell.
Whoa!
Are you naked?
I... I was hot.
Are you okay?
You're even more wasted than I am.
Come on, go to bed properly.
You were that hot
you had to take your underwear off?
No, I needed to pee.
I was probably drunk and just took it off.
Okay, okay. Be careful.
Namo.
What are you doing standing here alone?
Tulip.
Are you free this evening?
Why?
I wanna talk to you about something.
This evening...
I actually already have plans with Baikhaw.
Oh, okay.
We can talk later.
Come on, let's go.
See you.
I already told you.
I checked everything that night.
There's no footage of an attacker
like you said.
Maybe you could look a little harder?
Fine. I'll take another look for you.
W-Wait, stop right here.
Can you zoom in?
Zoom more... more...
What does Namo want to talk to you about?
I have no idea.
But he's been acting weird
ever since the night Wawwa got attacked.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Baikhaw!
- What the hell is wrong with you now?
- I know you're the one who did that to me.
- Wawwa!
Tulip. Look at this.
I have a clip.
Here.
This is the night before I got attacked.
She's right there in the footage.
Don't you think that's way too convenient?
This is my campus.
I'm allowed to go wherever I want.
Stop bullshitting.
You planted drugs on me.
You ruined my future.
I know you're not sincere with Tulip.
And that senior, Q...
The girl who almost slept with him
in his car?
That was you.
- Just stop lying...
- You're the liar.
I know everything now. It's you!
Everything you're saying?
You're the one who did it.
- What did I do?
- Wanna see yourself?
- Show me then.
- Fine. I'll show you.
Bring it.
What are you trying to do?
Watch it yourself.
Do you really like my friend?
Yeah, I do.
What about me? Do you like me?
You're the one who told me.
That with you, it's just for fun.
Tulip, it... it's not like that, okay?
Honestly, I didn't even want to say anything
at first.
But you were so damn annoying,
always picking fights with me.
So yeah, I had to say it.
I was just drunk that night.
Are you sure it was just once?
- Baikhaw!
- Wawwa!
Fine! I liked Q.
And we slept together.
But...
I knew Q wanted to date you.
And he would never actually date me anyway.
So I backed off.
Why didn't you tell me from the start?
I wanted you to be happy.
And I wanted Q to be happy too.
Wow... Miss Goody two-shoes.
So you let your friend take
whatever scraps were left over after you.
No! I never thought of it like that.
- Or you just wanted to win...
- No!
Oh? Then what?
- I just wanted you to be happy.
- Really?
If your life's a mess, fine.
Be a mess by yourself.
Why drag your friend down with you?
And look, I'm not even trying to be mean,
but people like you...
You don't deserve to be her friend.
Tulip, please, listen to me.
I was wrong about this, yes.
But... about Baikhaw, she hurt me.
She's ly...
Stop talking!
This whole time, I've always defended you.
But today, I think I'm done.
Come on, let's go.
Tulip!
- Tulip!
- No more Tulip for you.
Tulip!
I never thought
things would turn out like this.
We were so close, you know?
I trusted everything she ever said.
Why would she do this to me?
Why did she have to lie to me?
Don't cry. What are you crying for?
I feel like I don't have anyone left.
I just have you.
You're my only real friend.
From now on, whatever happens, just tell me.
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
Tough day today.
I just realized something.
When you cut off a friend you've had forever,
this is what it feels like.
All this time,
I always believed that
if you're real with someone,
they'll be real with you.
But now I'm not so sure anymore.
I'm really glad
that I have you and Baikhaw with me now.
If I didn't have you two,
I think I'd be way worse off.
With everything, my parents... my friend...
Especially when it's my close friend.
I don't even know how I'd get through it.
- Dad!
- It's late. What took you so long?
I was studying with my friends.
Are you sure you weren't with some boy?
Seriously, what are you doing here?
Why are you picking a fight with me?
I've tried calling you every day.
You never pick up.
Why would you do this to me?
Stop lying, Dad.
You never called me. Not once.
That's not true.
I never got a single missed call.
Wait, your number's blocked... but...
You'd go this far?
- I'm your father!
- I told you I didn't block you!
Maybe I pressed it by accident!
What the hell...
If you don't even respect me,
then fine. We're done.
Let's see how you survive without me.
Baikhaw...
I don't want to hurt Tulip anymore.
I can't. I can't just sleep with her.
Nail her and we'll be together.
Baikhaw and Tao, they are more than friends.
Tulip!
Hello, Namo.
Namo!