[whimsical theme song playing]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[twinkling chime]
- [air hissing]
- [ball pops]
[whimsical theme song continues]
[song concludes]
[fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
[animals calling]
[pants]
[birds chirping, calling]
[animal howling]
[quirky music playing]
[music fades]
- [wolf howls]
- [branches rustling]
[wind whistling]
[owl hooting]
[quirky music resumes]
[music stops]
[owl hooting]
[branches rustling]
[suspenseful musical sting plays]
[breathes shakily]
[quirky music resumes]
[Eun-ho] What the…
There's nothing in the bag.
- [screams]
- [suspenseful musical sting plays]
[music fades]
[breathes shakily]
You've been digging up this whole mountain
for three months straight.
[stammering] Who… are you?
Where is Hanyang?
- What?
- [Eun-ho] I need to get to Hanyang today.
So, tell me. Which way is it?
[quirky music resumes]
Hanyang is that way.
Oh, that way?
But it'll take at least 20 days
to get there.
- [music concludes]
- [suspenseful musical sting plays]
What?
[exhales]
[Eun-ho] Oh, I almost forgot.
- [screams]
- [quirky music resumes]
Dig that up
and brew it carefully for half a day.
It will help with your mother's illness.
What?
[echoing jingle]
[music concludes]
[bright musical sting plays]
[man chuckles]
[mysterious music playing]
[Eun-ho] This is an ancient tale.
[man] I found it!
[Eun-ho] It is the story
of a nine-tailed fox
who wished to become human,
spending her days cultivating virtue
on Myohyangsan Mountain.
- [music fades]
- [overlapping chatter]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful musical sting plays]
[echoing plop]
[Geum-ho] Can you leave us for a moment?
Chun-sim stays.
Chun-sim.
That's you!
What did you do with Chun-sim?
Pardon?
What do you…
Look.
It's so obvious.
[soft music playing]
[twinkling chime]
[chuckles softly]
You seemed completely human,
yet your cunning is all fox.
How did you know?
Your scent.
I smell the earth on you.
The scent of Myohyangsan Mountain's soil
that I've known for centuries.
Have you been well?
I was just bored without you around.
By the way, don't worry about Chun-sim.
I bet she's dozing off in the kitchen.
All right.
How do you feel?
It's your long-awaited wedding day.
It still doesn't feel real
that I've become human
and will be wed to my beloved.
Goodness.
Fine, leave me behind
and go live a happy life.
Come here, Eun-ho.
Let me hug you. It's been a while.
Geum-ho…
[chuckles]
[twinkling chime]
[music fades]
[musicians playing jaunty music]
[chicken clucking]
[Eun-ho] This is usually
where old tales end.
She finally became human
and married the one she loved.
And so, they lived happily ever after.
The end.
[children laughing, chattering]
Get over here!
[tender music playing]
Wow, amazing.
[gasps]
Look at this.
These hairpins must be new.
Oh my gosh, they're so pretty!
Don't they look good on me?
[music rises]
- Geum-ho?
- Yes?
What's got you staring like that?
Well, look at you.
What?
[tutting]
So that's why
you wanted to come to the market.
You had an ulterior motive.
It's not like that.
If you're done looking, let's go.
My lady!
So we meet again.
Yes, my lord.
What a coincidence running into you.
[tender music continues]
[overlapping chatter]
Be happy, Geum-ho.
[music falls]
[thunder rumbling]
[mysterious music playing]
[raindrops tapping]
- [rain pattering]
- [Eun-ho] But I didn't know then…
[mysterious music continues]
[soldier] That way!
[Eun-ho] …that human life
is endlessly fragile,
and their happiness
shatters far too easily.
That life is hard,
and death is always near.
That was the future that awaited.
So in the end,
Geum-ho would not find happiness.
[thunder rumbles]
[Eun-ho] All because she loved a human
and chose to become one.
PRESENT DAY
[sirens wailing in distance]
[Eun-ho] And so, I became who I am today.
A nine-tailed fox
who refuses to love humans
and does not seek to become one.
That's who I am.
[echoing rumbling whoosh]
[ethereal voice vocalizing]
[Eun-ho] Why should I want
to become a human?
So trivial, powerless, aging, sickly,
and in the end, doomed to die.
Here and now,
one life ends…
and another begins.
[music intensifies]
[Eun-ho] And this story began
nine years ago.
- [thunder crashing]
- [twinkling chime]
EPISODE 1
AN INEVITABLE EVENT
[music concludes]
[player 1] Here! Over here!
SOSIN HIGH SCHOOL
[gentle music playing]
HYEON WOO-SEOK
[player 1] Pass! Over there!
[player 2] Cover! I'm coming through!
NINE YEARS AGO
That's it!
He's good, isn't he?
That's Hyeon Woo-seok.
He just became a high school senior.
[translating into Spanish]
[in Korean] Since he was
first selected for the U-13 national team,
he has been the starting striker
across all youth squads.
[Yeon-su translating into Spanish]
- Hey, Woo-seok! Pass!
- [Yeon-su continues translating]
- [player 1] Pass!
- [player 2] Cover this side!
Hey! You crazy idiot!
Woo-seok was open!
Stop messing around
and just pass the ball!
[speaks Spanish]
He's asking who that player is.
[Yong-gil] Which one?
[Yeon-su] That one.
The one who was messing around earlier.
- [Si-yeol] That's a foul!
- That's Kang Si-yeol.
Gosh, that kid is just crazy.
He's all flash and no substance.
And he never passes.
He tries to do everything himself.
[music turns exciting]
Hey, Si-yeol, you brat! Just tap it in!
Stop showing off!
[ball whooshing]
- [players cheering]
- [music concludes]
Damn, that little…
Woo-seok, nice assist.
- Assist.
- [players cheering]
[Yong-gil clapping]
You think what a coach says is a joke?
I told you to pass to Woo-seok
whenever you get the ball.
The new youth national team coach
came to watch Woo-seok play today.
The least you could do
is help your friend,
not get in his way.
How is me scoring a goal
getting in Woo-seok's way?
[angrily]
So why did you have to score a goal?
I told you to play defense today.
When did I tell you to score a goal?
You got carried away trying to stand out.
Straighten up.
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
You've never even paid
your club fees on time,
and you give me this attitude.
[grunts]
[Sang-cheol] Good work.
- [Yong-gil] Hey, boys.
- Eat up.
[Yong-gil] Woo-seok's father
is treating us,
so make sure you thank him
before digging in.
[Sang-cheol] Gosh, Coach.
There's really no need.
[laughs]
- Here, have some more.
- Hey, Kang Si-yeol.
LET'S GO, SOSIN SOCCER CLUB!
[Woo-seok] Dad, hold on.
- Sure.
- Hold this.
- Kang Si-yeol.
- It's fine. I don't want any.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
[Sang-cheol] Coach.
[coach] Yes, good to see you.
- [Sang-cheol] Great game today.
- Not at all.
Here, use this to take the boys out
for a nice dinner next time.
Thank you as always, Mr. Hyeon.
[coach and Sang-cheol laugh]
- [coach] Thank you.
- [Sang-cheol] It's nothing.
- [coach chuckles]
- [cleat thudding]
[reporter over radio]
The contractor for Bannam Zone 2,
Korea's biggest redevelopment project,
will be named today.
With three top-tier construction companies
competing for the contract,
experts say Geumsu Construction,
embroiled in a power abuse scandal,
is unlikely to win, leaving the other two
as front-runners.
- In other news--
- [radio beeps, shuts off]
Why did you turn it off?
I was listening to it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lee.
Should I turn it back on?
[sighs, clicks tongue]
The real issue isn't abuse of power.
It's subordinates getting out of line.
I pay you to drive,
so why aren't you focused on driving?
Mr. Lee, it's not that--
Are your ears perking up
because they're trashing me on the radio?
- No, sir.
- [tense music playing]
That's not it at all.
- [Yoon] It's a red light.
- [tires screeching]
- What the heck?
- [pedestrians gasp]
[pedestrian] Watch where you're going!
[sighs]
2016 SEOUL
BANNAM ZONE 2 PROJECT PLAN
[scoffs]
It fell. What bad luck.
- [music concludes]
- [tires screeching]
WELCOME TO THE CONTRACTOR SELECTION
GENERAL MEETING
Did you drive here yourself?
I ended up driving myself.
Mr. Lee, there's also
the board's decision to consider.
- Are you sure about this?
- [sighs]
You mean those old geezers
telling me to stay put?
There's no need
for you to get involved, sir.
It was always going to be
a difficult contract to win.
Now there's a risk that
you might have to take all the blame.
This is why you're just an employee.
[tense music playing]
- Just take off your shirt.
- Yes, sir.
- Should I hire a new driver?
- Sure, whatever.
Just give him some money
so he doesn't run his mouth.
Yes, sir.
[scoffs]
This project is mine.
I want every son of a bitch
in the sticks to know
that Lee Yoon of Geumsu Group
personally won a 9.5-trillion-won project.
Then those old geezers won't be able
to call me a deadbeat anymore.
[Secretary Choi] Mr. Lee.
Now is a crucial time,
with the group's succession on the line.
If you fail to win the contract--
You know that saying,
"there's nothing money can't buy"?
I used to think
that was just an expression.
But I was wrong.
There's nothing that money can't solve.
Seriously, anything's possible with money.
[chuckles]
[tense music continues]
[executive] Dear fellow members
of the Bannam Zone 2 union,
To begin, we,
the executive team of Yeoni Construction,
would like to extend our deepest respects
to the union members.
[crowd cheering]
BANNAM ZONE 2 CONSTRUCTION PROJECT PLAN
What, a deep bow? Give me a break.
[sighs]
YEONI CONSTRUCTION
- [touchpad clicks]
- [computer beeps]
- [audience murmuring]
- [computer error beeps]
I'm sorry, sir.
Hey, what did you do?
- Aren't they starting?
- [man 1] What's going on?
- [keyboard clacking]
- [tapping teeth]
- [man 2] Jeez.
- [man 1] What are they doing?
[audience murmuring]
[man 1] What's this?
Did they hire another celebrity?
[Eun-ho] My dear humans.
Allow me to intrude for a bit.
What is going on right now?
- What…
- Who's she?
It's a little noisy.
Don't panic.
Starting now, you will lose your voices.
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
[quirky music playing]
Now, everyone focus on me.
Don't think of anything else.
[fingers snap]
[twinkling chime]
[chime fades]
[fox squealing]
[microphone whines]
Ah, ah.
I'm sure you're all very busy,
so I'll make this quick.
You must all be stressing over
who to vote for to make more money.
But really, does it even matter
who builds the new Bannam-dong apartments?
Don't overthink it.
Everyone on the left side,
just vote for Geumsu Construction.
As for everyone on the right,
do as you please.
Well then.
[music concludes]
[sighs] Oh, right.
Honestly, I feel a little bad.
I have a general idea of how much
you humans love your apartments.
But what can I do?
I have to make money too.
I'm sure you all understand
since we all love money.
Right? Bye then.
- [quirky music continues]
- [microphone thuds, echoes]
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
You. Follow me.
[music concludes]
- [crickets chirping]
- [traffic rumbling in distance]
[dogs barking]
[sniffs]
[pants]
[dogs barking]
[Bok-sun grunting]
- [cart creaks]
- Oh dear.
[tender music playing]
[Bok-sun] Goodness.
- [Si-yeol] Grandma, let me.
- What?
All right, let's go.
[Si-yeol panting]
[Bok-sun groans]
I scored a goal today.
Oh my, well done.
[pants]
- Is that it?
- What else should I say?
I'm just saying "well done"
because you did well.
[chuckles] My goodness, Grandma.
If you keep this up,
I won't spoil you when I'm older.
[chuckles]
I don't care about that.
Well, I care.
Just you wait.
By the way, when do we need to pay
this month's soccer club fee?
I told you not to worry about that.
I'm exempt from the fees.
I'm the star player, you know.
[chuckles] Still,
that's not how things should be.
Grandma, haven't you heard
of a full scholarship?
I don't have to pay a single penny.
Gosh, really?
- Oh, my little boy, I'm so proud of you.
- [Si-yeol laughs]
[Bok-sun chuckles]
- [engine revving]
- [music concludes]
[upbeat pop song playing]
- Enjoy your meal. Take care.
- [woman 1] Thank you.
Here you go. Be safe!
[upbeat pop song continues]
[woman 2 speaking indistinctly]
Enjoy your meal.
SPEEDY DELIVERY SERVICE
[upbeat pop song continues]
Thank you.
[song concludes]
[Si-yeol] What are you doing at this hour?
[Woo-seok scoffs]
What about you?
And what's with that outfit?
I'm working my part-time job.
- What?
- I've got my eye on some cleats.
Jeez, you should be spending
your time practicing.
Just ask your parents for the cleats.
[ball thuds]
[Woo-seok] Hmm?
- [Si-yeol grunts]
- [yelps]
- Hey, wanna make a bet?
- Jeez.
[scoffs, sighs]
[in English] Okay.
[in Korean] What are the stakes?
[upbeat rock song playing]
[grunts]
- [Si-yeol grunts]
- [Woo-seok laughs]
[upbeat rock song continues]
- Oh!
- [grunts]
[laughs]
- [Woo-seok] Hey, that was a clear foul!
- [Si-yeol] Goal!
- You're out.
- [laughs]
[upbeat rock song continues]
[Si-yeol grunts]
[sighs]
Goal!
- Left.
- [Si-yeol] Right.
[grunts]
[upbeat rock song continues]
It went in, right?
- [gasps]
- [Si-yeol laughs]
Goal!
[cheers]
- [song concludes]
- [microwave buzzing]
[microwave beeping]
[Si-yeol] Nice.
[Woo-seok] Mm.
I was wondering why you were playing
like your life depended on it.
But is that it? A chicken breast?
I wasn't playing like that.
I just crushed you with my skills.
- [bones crack]
- [groans]
What? Are you hurt?
Hey, just hurry up and eat.
I want to get a few more deliveries in.
Mm.
What, is this your thing?
A lazy genius?
I mean, you don't seem to be taking
private lessons like everyone else.
And you're working part-time at this hour.
[inhales sharply]
But seeing you in action…
[slurps]
[yelps]
You asshole!
Hey.
A poor genius.
What?
You got the genius part right,
but I'm a bit short on cash.
My parents aren't around,
and my grandma's sick.
I see.
So while you're practicing,
I have to be out making money.
[clears throat] Hey, I didn't know--
But you know what's really important here?
Despite all that,
without any of those damn private lessons,
- I still managed to kick your ass today.
- [scoffs]
You saw the goal I scored
during practice today, right?
Yeah, I saw it, you punk. [clicks tongue]
So don't get too cocky
just because you're on the national team.
[grunts mockingly]
When you get called up,
I'm gonna take your spot as striker.
Mm.
When you get back, the starting lineup
might be totally different.
Why am I even talking to you?
Jeez.
[slurps]
Man, that's good.
You really don't want any?
I don't eat stuff like that.
[gentle classical music playing]
[finger tapping]
[finger tapping rapidly]
[Eun-ho] Why aren't you eating?
That poor cow died for nothing.
I don't have an appetite.
I told you,
there's nothing to worry about.
This is important to me.
I'm sure it is.
You acted like a deadbeat,
and now you're
on your rich father's bad side.
And now your position as heir is at risk.
[scoffs]
You seem pretty interested
in human affairs.
Because I've taken a liking to you.
[fox squealing]
You're rich,
and you look like a troublemaker.
I think you're going to become
a repeat customer.
Since we're on the subject,
who are your other clients besides me?
[snickers]
You seem pretty interested
in nine-tailed fox affairs.
Can I have this one too?
[plate thuds]
I guess that's a secret.
[clicks tongue]
Then, what exactly are you capable of?
Judging by the fact that you need money,
it seems you can't do whatever you want.
Shouldn't I know
what you can and can't do
if I'm going to hire you again?
[snickers]
Humans are always like this.
All right, let me explain something.
[rumbling whoosh]
- [gasps]
- [thunder rumbles, crashes]
- [yells]
- [tense music playing]
[echoing whoosh]
[screams, whimpers]
What is this?
[breathes heavily]
Where am I?
I guess calling you a "customer"
gave you the wrong idea.
That if you just give me money,
you can order me to do anything
and ask for whatever you want.
[huffs]
[screams]
[scream echoing]
[screaming]
[twinkling chime]
Simply put,
think of this less as making requests
and more like praying.
Whether or not I grant your wish
is up to me.
And how I choose to grant it
is also up to me.
How much I take,
and what I take as payment,
is obviously up to me as well.
I'm the one who asks questions, not you.
Even what you're allowed to know,
and how much, is up to me.
Do you understand now?
I'm telling you not to get cocky.
You pathetic little human.
[rumbling whoosh]
[classical music resumes]
But since we're on the subject,
I'll tell you one thing.
I have only one principle.
I avoid doing
even the smallest of good deeds
and only avoid doing major misdeeds.
[chuckles]
Looks like you didn't get it.
This is important,
so I'll break it down for you.
I don't do good deeds.
No matter how trivial.
I can't risk cultivating more virtue
and accidentally becoming human.
As for wrongdoings,
I only avoid major ones.
Things like…
killing people.
That's the only thing I avoid.
I'm trying to avoid becoming human,
not trying to diminish my spiritual power.
SECRETARY CHOI
[cell phone buzzing]
[cell phone continues buzzing]
[Eun-ho] You can go now.
The voting results are out.
You should go get your picture taken.
Nothing beats a photo for showing off.
By the way, I already took the money
from the trunk of your car.
- So don't worry about it.
- [cell phone buzzing]
[motorbike engine revving]
[brakes squeal]
[wistful music playing]
[Bok-sun grunts softly]
[Eun-ho] A human's life
is like swimming in a sea of suffering.
[wistful music continues]
[Eun-ho] From the moment they're thrown
into this unfamiliar world
until they rot away to nothing,
humans can never find
even a moment of peace.
[coos]
[Eun-ho] Life is a constant competition.
It's a battlefield
where they can only climb up
by dragging others down.
And it's a hamster wheel
that never stops turning.
[crosswalk signal beeping]
[Eun-ho] Human happiness
is but a fleeting illusion,
and such is the human condition
I have observed for hundreds of years.
But in contrast to that,
my life as a nine-tailed fox
is like a festival that never ends.
[upbeat electronic music playing]
- [snickers]
- [fox squealing]
Hey.
Yes?
All the kids these days
seem to dress like you.
I used to dress like that 20 years ago.
- I guess it's back in style.
- Excuse me?
You.
Come shopping with me today.
Why should I?
Because I like the way you dress.
Besides, it's boring to shop alone.
Think of yourself
as a friend for the day, if you will.
What the heck?
What a weirdo.
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
[Eun-ho] Listen to me.
You're going to hang out with me today.
Yes, of course.
- [fox squealing]
- [music concludes]
So, you're saying
you're a nine-tailed fox?
Really?
Come on, a nine-tailed fox?
There's no such thing.
You'd believe me if I used sorcery
and showed you my tails,
but I can't be bothered.
- [fingers snap]
- Just believe it. I'm a nine-tailed fox.
- Oh, okay.
- [whimsical music playing]
Oh my! Those look great on you too.
You think so?
I'll take these too.
Hey, I have a question.
What is it?
"Aren't nine-tailed foxes
supposed to eat human livers
and seduce men to drain their life force?"
Yes, how did you know?
It was obvious.
Do you think you're the first human
to ask me such questions?
Do you know how people
in the Joseon era used to speak?
You think they were like…
[dramatically] "Your Majesty,"
"How insolent"?
Do you really think that?
They didn't?
That's all just made up
by those TV people.
[scoffs]
It's not as if they actually
lived through that era like I did.
So how would they know?
You make something up,
and humans just believe it.
Same with the tales
about nine-tailed foxes.
[woman] My goodness, that's truly amazing.
Look at everything happening
inside that little box.
- My goodness, how fascinating!
- [overlapping chatter]
RETURN OF THE LEGEND
NINE-TAILED FOX
[Eun-ho]
People didn't think of us in this way
before that damn Return of the Legend.
- [wolf howls over TV]
- [overlapping chatter continues]
[suspenseful music playing over TV]
- [dramatic sting over TV]
- [group shrieks, whimpers]
[woman] Oh my gosh.
That scared the life out of me.
[snarls]
[quirky music playing]
[Eun-ho] When humans cultivate themselves,
they're called sages,
while animals that do so
are called spirit beasts.
So why do foxes cultivating themselves
to become human get treated like monsters?
Do they think it's easy to self-cultivate
and train until we grow nine tails?
Nine-tailed foxes cultivate themselves?
Yes, just like how sages self-cultivate
and train to become immortals,
nine-tailed foxes have to self-cultivate
and train to become humans.
Think about it.
Why would a nine-tailed fox,
who's self-cultivating and building karma,
hunt human livers? If they did that,
they would lose
all the spiritual power they've earned.
- [sighs]
- Oh, I see.
You must have felt so misunderstood.
[sighs] Anyway, that's all in the past.
I'm the only nine-tailed fox
left on Earth now.
I've lost all desire to be human,
so I have no reason to cultivate myself.
You're not trying
to become human? [sniffs]
But you're a nine-tailed fox. How come?
Because I love the way I live now.
Sometimes, humans get the wrong idea.
They think that living forever
would be tedious and boring.
But when you actually experience it,
there's never a dull moment
because the human world changes so fast.
There's always something new and fun.
[echoing jingle]
- [overlapping chatter]
- [shoeshiner] Shoeshine! Shoeshine!
YEAR 1930
[shoeshiner] Shoeshine!
- It's English.
- [woman] At our academy…
YEJEONG ACADEMY
ENGLISH
YOUR WEAPON FOR SUCCESS!
[Eun-ho] So this is how Westerners write?
This looks like it'd be fun.
[in English] "I am a girl."
[students] "I am a girl."
"You are a boy."
[students] "You are a boy."
Okay, you ladies are doing a great job.
Now, let's practice with each other. Okay?
[in Korean]
What did that Westerner just say?
- [quirky music sting plays]
- [Eun-ho clicks tongue]
Hey, Teacher.
Speak our language.
I can't understand a single word.
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
[in Korean] What did you just say?
How am I suddenly speaking
in Joseon language?
- Oh, Lord!
- [fox squealing]
YEAR 1970
COMICS
MARTIAL ARTS, ROMANCE
THE COUNT'S BLACK SHEEP
FINAL EPISODE
[upbeat retro pop music playing]
THE END
[Eun-ho] What?
The main character dies?
What kind of ending is this?
Hey, you. Comic artist.
- Hey, comic artist!
- [groans]
[intriguing music playing]
Who are you?
[echoing boing]
- [fox yipping]
- What's with this ending?
Is this the best you could do?
Draw it again!
- [breathes sharply]
- [fox howling]
THE COUNT'S BLACK SHEEP
FINAL EPISODE
[intriguing music continues]
- [gasps] What's happening?
- [suspenseful musical sting plays]
[faint twinkling chime]
THE END
[chuckles]
SPACE ARCADE
MAKKEULLAE RICKSHAW
- [Eun-ho] Ah!
- [lively chatter]
YEAR 1990
4TH NATIONAL GAMING TOURNAMENT
PRELIMINARY ROUND
- Ah, ah! Ah!
- [upbeat chiptune music playing]
- [buttons clacking]
- [game characters grunting]
Hey, stop it! Stop following me!
Ah!
- [fox howling]
- [game character screams]
You're such a cheap player.
- [fingers snap]
- Stop beating me.
Please, just stop.
[downbeat quirky music playing]
[music rises]
[game character grunting]
- [fox screaming]
- Hey, don't make it so obvious!
It's no fun now.
Do your best, okay?
- [fox yipping]
- Play better, but not to win.
Is that so hard?
- [music concludes]
- [woman] But, seriously,
is it really fun to live like that?
What?
I mean, what you're saying is
that in all that time,
you've never actually
accomplished anything.
What is that supposed to mean?
You don't think
I've accomplished anything?
I've learned everything
and played every game there is.
But no matter what you've learned,
you haven't followed through.
If there's something you don't like,
you just change it all.
- Or just scrap it.
- It's not like that.
[woman] And you don't have any friends
to shop and chat with,
so you just grab a random person and--
I said it's not like that!
- [twinkling chime]
- [Eun-ho] Hey, take my side.
No matter what.
[twinkling chime]
- I envy you.
- [babyish giggling]
[woman] I wish I could live like you.
Just spending money and having fun
without a care in the world.
[downbeat music playing]
[Eun-ho] What?
Yes? What is it?
Forget it. Just finish your food.
[scoffs] I really chose
the wrong person for this.
Can't she read the room at all?
- [scoffs]
- [woman chuckles softly]
[sighs]
[music concludes]
What is it?
Why did you drag me out on a weekend?
Pick one. Whichever.
What?
You said there were cleats
you wanted to buy.
Don't save up with your part-time job.
Just pick them now.
And if I do?
You're going to buy them for me?
[chuckles softly] No.
[scoffs]
I happen to have
a sponsorship deal with this brand.
It's a sponsorship
worth 20 million won a year,
but I can't use all of it
by myself anyway.
A sponsorship deal?
But you're not even a pro.
[Woo-seok scoffs]
Dude, I'm a top prospect
for the youth national team.
They signed me a few years ago.
Are you going to pick one or not?
Do you think I'm a beggar?
[pensive music playing]
What?
I'm fine.
I'm leaving.
- Hey…
- [music fades]
SONGWONGAK CHINESE RESTAURANT
That was so delicious.
Yeah, I guess you--
[rumbling whoosh]
[groans]
- [scoffs]
- [Si-yeol groans]
Humans are so pathetically weak.
Get up. Is anything broken?
No…
No, that's not it.
[running footsteps]
What happened?
But are you okay?
We ran into each other pretty hard.
You should try exercising
instead of just burying yourself in books.
You're pathetic for a guy your size.
Just go.
[Si-yeol] Oh…
My apologies.
- [camera shutters clicking]
- [mysterious music playing]
[crowd cheering]
KING RAMYEON
[mysterious music continues]
[scoffs] How interesting.
What is?
[Eun-ho] That human over there.
I think he'll become quite famous
in the near future.
Famous?
Which one of the two?
That one over there.
I see.
But how do you know things like that?
I just do.
I sometimes see fragments of the future.
I can't see them whenever I want.
I don't know when, why, or what I'll see,
but whatever I see is inevitable.
[ethereal voice vocalizing]
[thunder rumbling]
[tense music playing]
[soldier] That way!
[Eun-ho]
Even I can't do anything to change it.
[music concludes]
Anyway, that guy will become rich
and famous at some point.
So he might become one of my clients.
Oh, right.
You said you grant rich people's wishes
and get paid for it, didn't you?
Then, maybe you could grant my wish too?
You think I would do that?
You don't have nearly enough
to become my client.
- [downbeat music playing]
- But starting today, we're friends.
Don't you have, like,
a discount for friends and family?
[scoffs]
Humans never fail to disappoint.
This is exactly why I don't bother
with troublesome human relationships.
I told you earlier.
You're just a friend for the day.
What?
What that means is…
- [twinkling chime]
- …you're going to forget
everything you did with me today,
everything we talked about,
and even my very existence.
- Understand?
- [twinkling chime]
Yes, I understand.
Anyway, I had fun today.
You should get going too.
Hey, you guys.
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
Come carry this for me.
[music concludes]
[lights fizz, slam off]
[mysterious traditional music playing]
[breathes shakily]
[lights slamming on]
[mysterious stranger]
You're a beast cultivating yourself.
What in the world are you doing here?
[echoing whoosh]
[exhales sharply]
[faint dramatic musical sting plays]
- [music fades]
- [Woo-seok] Hey.
Are you really mad?
Look, it wasn't because
I felt sorry for you.
Hey, come on.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
I guess now that I think about it,
I did feel sorry for you.
But it's not because I think
I'm better than you or anything.
I just wanted to help you out
after what you told me.
[Si-yeol exhales]
Hey.
- What?
- Wanna kick the ball around a bit?
What?
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Sure, bring it on.
[intriguing music playing]
[phone camera clicks]
At cafés, you have to buy
one drink per person.
That's the rule
in the human world these days.
I'm…
[inhales] …a being far greater
than any rule made by humans.
I'm sure you are.
After all,
you're the Deity of the Big Dipper.
What brings you here all of a sudden,
interrupting my hobby like this?
You call that a hobby?
Of course. There isn't anything
more human and fun than spending money.
[Pagun exhales heavily]
If you enjoy living like a human so much,
why won't you become one,
while deceiving the eyes of Heaven?
You're missing the point.
Who said I want to live like a human?
Squeezing into the subway to go to work
and working for over ten hours a day,
only to collapse into sleep
from exhaustion.
Even if you make a few bucks like that,
you don't have time to spend it.
That's what it means to be human.
A moment of sweetness,
and a lifetime of bitterness.
[Pagun sighs]
But life as a nine-tailed fox is kind of
like spending money on a pay-to-win game.
You get to enjoy all the fun stuff
without any of the inconvenience.
I wonder if the big shots up there
would even understand what I'm saying.
Since they're just so divine and all.
You're still wicked and irreverent.
Oh, whatever.
Anyway, I don't think we're
on good enough terms to sit and chat.
Let's just get straight to the point,
Lord Pagun.
So?
You want me to become human already?
Are you asking why I'm still like this
when all the other nine-tailed foxes
have already become human,
lived out their lives, and died?
- [hand thuds]
- [Eun-ho] I refuse.
If that's all, I can go now, right?
I'm going to go home
and unbox my new stuff.
[Pagun] Your scale
is tipping.
[tense music playing]
[scoffs]
That can't be.
I put an insane amount of effort
into keeping that balance aligned.
I even earn my own money
just to appease all of you up there.
So how could the scale be tipping?
There will come a time
when you must choose.
Whether to become human
or be forever annihilated.
[chuckles]
Don't make me laugh.
They may be deities,
but how dare they threaten me?
Let them try.
Do they still think I'm the same
naive fox who believed everything
the ones above told me?
They won't get their way.
Even you guys don't really get
the so-called Law of Heaven, do you?
Because it's so vague and messed up.
Well, there's one thing
I know for certain.
"Heaven's net is vast and wide,
yet nothing slips through."
You may think
you're outside of Heaven's influence,
but nothing ever escapes notice.
[music intensifies]
Ha!
Save the sermon.
[music concludes]
That was Daoist teaching, actually.
[energetic dance music playing]
[overlapping chatter]
[server] Excuse me.
[hand slams]
- Get up!
Mr. Lee!
[group] We love you!
[employee]
You're the only boss we have, sir!
[utensils clattering]
[group chanting] Lee Yoon!
What was that? I can't hear you.
Louder!
[group chanting] Lee Yoon!
Everyone, drink up!
[group] Drink up!
[music concludes]
[uplifting pop rock music playing]
[both panting]
[Si-yeol grunts]
[Woo-seok in English] Nice.
[Si-yeol] Hey, are you okay?
[groans]
Gosh, let's call it a day.
[Si-yeol] Hey, it's my turn though.
[Woo-seok] Damn it.
Fine.
- [whistling whoosh]
- [Si-yeol sighs]
- [music concludes]
- [Eun-ho] Unbelievable.
I can't believe they're still
trying to boss me around at my age.
Today just keeps getting worse--
[gasps]
What? [yells] Who was that?
[breathes heavily]
[scoffs]
[Woo-seok] Wow, it was like a missile.
Hey, I'll go find the ball.
You go on ahead.
- I'll come with you.
- It's fine. You go.
Bye.
[crickets chirping]
Man, where did it go?
[Eun-ho] Was it you?
[quirky music playing]
Are you the owner of this ball?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
- Wait.
- No need to thank me.
[bang]
- Hey--
- Go. We're done here.
Excuse me!
Wait, you're that kid from earlier.
Were you kicking a ball around this late
because I told you to get some exercise?
You don't look it,
but you're quite obedient.
What is she talking about?
Anyway, you shouldn't go around
popping other people's balls.
Well, I couldn't pop your head, could I?
Since I'm a self-cultivated beast.
[scoffs] Unbelievable.
[sighs]
Hold on.
They don't usually pop that easily.
It's not some kind of balloon--
That's because you are a weak human.
[Si-yeol] What did you say?
Wait, who do you keep calling weak?
Can't you tell just by looking?
I'm an athlete.
Is that so?
[Si-yeol] I may not be much now,
but in a few years,
I'm going to be a really famous athlete.
[Eun-ho sarcastically] Right.
- I don't think so.
- [echoing jingle]
- What?
- [woman] Famous?
- [pensive music playing]
- Which one of the two?
[Eun-ho] That one over there.
Maybe your friend, but not you.
I saw it earlier.
What are you--
Your friend is going to be very famous.
He'll be a world-class player
and make a lot of money too.
I'm certain. The future
never changes after I've seen it.
But as for you…
- Hmm…
- [twinkling chime]
- [inhales deeply]
- [echoing boing]
I don't see anything at all.
Who are you to say that?
You don't know anything about me!
You'll just be a nobody.
You might become a mediocre player
no one remembers,
but any success beyond that…
[tutting]
It's just not in your future.
So don't get your hopes up
and dream too big.
That way, you won't get hurt.
[gasps] This…
This woman is a complete lunatic.
It's cruel, I know. [sighs dramatically]
But that's just how human life is.
It's not like life is being
especially cruel to you.
So don't take it too hard.
[gasps, sighs]
[tense music playing]
[slurring] Man, I did it! Damn it!
I'm Lee Yoon. Who's going to stop me?
[hooting]
[car roof thumping]
- Move! Damn it!
- [car horn honks]
Whoa!
[tires screeching]
[clicks tongue]
- [music intensifies]
- [crosswalk signal beeping]
[tires screeching]
[car crashes]
[music concludes]
[tires screech]
- Did you hear that?
- I don't know.
Maybe there was an accident.
It has nothing to do with me.
[ominous musical sting plays]
- [tense music playing]
- [Yoon] Oh no, oh no… What…
[sighs heavily]
[gasps]
[Yoon] I have to get out of here.
[engine revs]
- [Si-yeol] Hey!
- [tires screeching]
Stop! I said stop!
Damn it. [pants]
- [tires screeching]
- I said stop! [pants]
- [whimpers]
- [tense music continues]
[pants]
Woo-seok!
Woo-seok.
- [siren blares, fades]
- [tense music continues]
OPERATING ROOM
[nurse] You can't come in.
[pants heavily]
PLEASE DISPOSE OF TRASH HERE
[Yoon] Damn it.
[music concludes]
[Yoon] Jeez.
[breathes shakily]
Seriously.
[scoffs]
What am I going to do?
[breathes heavily]
[mutters]
[exhales shakily]
It'll probably be fine.
[sirens wailing]
[Si-yeol] He seemed drunk.
He was stumbling when he walked.
[Ji-seong] So you suspect
he was intoxicated.
Okay, we've requested
all the security footage from the area,
so we'll identify the vehicle owner soon.
[sighs]
[groans]
- How may I help you?
- [Bong-chang] Well, I…
Yesterday, I…
ran someone over.
[dramatic musical sting plays]
[Secretary Choi]
Bong-chang just went to turn himself in.
[Yoon sighs]
[Secretary Choi] There won't be
any problems for you, sir.
[dark intriguing music playing]
[Si-yeol] It's not him.
It wasn't this guy.
I saw him.
[Ji-seong sighs]
- Sir.
- Yes?
[Ji-seong] Are you sure
you were the one driving?
Yes. I secretly took a company car out,
- and made a mistake--
- You're lying.
You weren't the one
who caused the accident.
[grunts] I saw everything!
Why are you lying? Seriously!
Let go of me!
[Secretary Choi] Sir, we have a problem.
Bong-chang just called.
He said he couldn't bring himself to lie
and asked if we could just forget the deal
in exchange for returning
all the money we gave him.
What are you talking about?
Why the sudden change?
He said there was a witness.
[dark intriguing music continues]
Bring that bastard here right now.
- There's one more thing--
- What is it this time?
[Secretary Choi]
I received a call from the police station.
They said you also need to come in
for questioning as a witness, sir.
[music turns tense]
[Yoon breathes shakily]
[yells] How the hell are you…
[sighs heavily] Damn it!
How could you handle this so poorly?
I apologize, sir.
[scoffs, mutters]
[sighs]
Get out.
[Secretary Choi] Pardon?
[music concludes]
I'll handle it myself from now on.
Get out.
[Secretary Choi] Mm-hmm.
[door opens]
- [Yoon] Jeez.
- [door closes]
[sighs]
[lock chimes, clicks]
[drawer closes]
[faint twinkling chime]
I WILL GRANT YOUR WISH
[lighter lid clicks]
[rumbling whoosh]
[Yoon yelps]
[mysterious music playing]
[Yoon groans]
[groans]
[grunts]
- Wow.
- [footsteps approaching]
It's you again.
[chuckles]
It must be nice to be rich,
summoning me again after just one day.
Maybe I didn't charge you
enough yesterday.
[snickers]
This time, it's a very simple job.
But it's urgent.
What a shame.
I was thinking of taking a break
for about ten years.
[sighs] An annoying old geezer
has been pestering me lately.
So, I'm rejecting your request.
I'll pay you double
what I gave you yesterday.
I guess I'll rest
after I handle this quickly.
What is it?
URI GARAM HOSPITAL
[music concludes]
[sighs heavily]
[EKG monitor beeping]
[Si-yeol] Who are you?
You again?
It seems we're deeply connected by fate.
The soccer ball from yesterday, right?
But how did you know I was here?
Right.
I'm here to tweak your memory a bit.
What?
Look straight at me. Don't look away.
- [fingers snap]
- [twinkling chime]
About what you saw last night…
[inhales]
[ethereal voice vocalizing]
[crowd cheering]
[Eun-ho] Wait a minute.
- [vocalizing fades]
- This can't be happening.
[moody pop song playing]
[gasps]
No way.
Their fates have switched?
- [gasps]
- [tense musical sting plays]
What is this now?
[Pagun]
You're still wicked and irreverent.
[breathes shakily]
- [echoing chime]
- [Pagun] Your scale
is tipping.
[moody pop song continues]
- [song fades]
- [fox squealing]
NO TAIL TO TELL
[Eun-ho] I said I lost a huge chunk
of my spiritual power.
- You're going to help me.
- [upbeat pop song playing]
I mean, what are you exactly?
[Eun-ho] This beauty. And this mystique.
- A demon?
- A nine-tailed fox!
But no matter how much
I think about it, I just don't get it.
What did I do that was so wrong?
A human has died. Because of you.
[in English] Who are we?
[Eun-ho in Korean] Kang Si-yeol.
How much does he really make?
[woman] Apparently,
he makes 500 million won a week.
I'm so proud that I am me.
Long time no see, Si-yeol.
- Did he seriously not recognize me?
- [fans cheering]
[scoffs loudly]
You want to catch that hit-and-run driver
and make him pay, right?
I killed someone!
- Jeez!
- [Eun-ho] So, tell me. Whatever it is.
What's your wish?
Subtitle translation by Susanna Kim