=The Truth=
=Episode 11=
Si Yuanlong.
What is it?
Nothing.
Do you remember our bet last time?
Of course. What do you want me to do?
Let me be clear.
Don't push it.
I wouldn't.
It's actually about that volunteer event
the No-Name Diner keeps organizing.
I want you to join in.
Are you interested in it?
Just that?
So did you ask me,
or did he let you ask me?
Well...
Since when do you care
who asks you to volunteer?
What?
If I ask you, you won't go?
But if Little Qian asks, you'll go?
It's Little Qian who asks.
Fine. I'll go.
Volunteering is a good thing.
I'm really speechless.
Alright then, go ahead. I'm heading out.
Remember to go.
(Roman International)
Chen Zhi.
We have some questions.
Based on DNA comparison,
the deceased is your father,
Chen Daning.
He's really dead?
Then just do whatever you have to do.
What kind of attitude is that?
He was your biological father.
Right.
Biologically. And that's all.
You're not suspecting me, are you?
Our shop's anniversary is this month.
I'm busy all day long.
At the shop by day,
back to the dorm at night.
My manager and colleagues
can vouch for me.
Nothing more to say. I'm leaving.
Wait.
Tell us about Chen Daning.
Like what?
What could I possibly say?
Then we'll talk at the police station.
What about your mother? Tell us.
She died the year I graduated.
Why?
Haven't you investigated long enough
to know exactly
what kind of scum Chen Daning was?
I don't want to say
a single word about him.
If you really want to know,
go ask around the village.
I left as soon as my mom died.
He was never a father to me.
Who was your father
close to in the village?
Who'd want to be close to him?
Everyone avoided him like the plague.
Only the wife of Xie, that simple-minded
woman, was fooled by him all day.
Is Xie also a villager in Shipu Village?
By the name of Xie Hanguo.
He used to run an oil mill.
Is that oil mill still running?
It was shut down after he died.
He died?
He died long ago.
He got hit
crossing the highway years ago.
It happened many years ago.
From what you're saying,
Xie Hanguo's wife and Chen Daning
had an improper relationship?
Xie Hanguo found
that simple-minded woman somewhere.
She wasn't quite right up here.
It's said she didn't
even know her own name.
Xie Hanguo wasn't too bright either.
No idea where he found
that simple-minded woman.
As soon as Xie Hanguo died,
Chen Daning latched onto her.
Well, it might not be fair.
He was definitely tricking her
and after the money Xie Hanguo
saved up from his oil mill.
Do you know anything else
about Xie Hanguo's wife?
Well, she's dead too.
She and Xie had a son.
He's in his twenties now.
I forgot his real name.
Everyone in the village
just calls him Xie the Idiot.
If there's nothing else, I'm leaving.
They'll dock my pay for being out.
Xie Wenle,
resident of Shipu Village, 24 years old.
Both of his parents are deceased.
Regarding Xie Wenle's recent activities,
we've pulled his call records.
But we've found no valuable leads yet.
Our colleagues went to Shipu Village
to investigate.
Xie Wenle has been withdrawn
since childhood
and always keeps to himself.
He doesn't seem close to anyone.
Is there a car registered
under his name?
No.
No driver's license either.
About Chen Daning,
what did they say over in Shipu Village?
Chen Daning
was known throughout the area
as a drunk and a gambler.
He was lazy and shiftless.
He relied entirely
on his wife's farming to get by.
After learning of Chen Daning's affair
with Xie Wenle's mother,
his wife drank pesticide
and killed herself.
Not long after Xie Hanguo passed away,
Chen Daning moved in
with Xie Wenle's mother.
It's said he was after the money
Xie Hanguo left behind.
What was the relationship like
between Chen Daning and Xie Wenle?
We don't have many leads on that yet.
Captain Leng,
we'll verify all these details,
including Xie Wenle's connection
to Chen Daning,
Xie Wenle's biological mother,
and Xie Hanguo's financial status.
Right now, the forensic unit
is screening vehicles on the dump route.
But there are no results yet.
Chief Xu.
Should we suspend Ye Qian's duties
in the Major Crimes Unit for now?
I'm worried he can't handle both.
I trust him.
Okay.
Panicking won't help.
We have to search slowly, right?
Yeah.
Take a few days off.
Think of it as giving yourself a break.
Wouldn't that be nice?
It'll be good for your health.
Get yourself back in shape.
Then we can welcome the next chef
and go all out. Right?
Right?
Found it!
No, not a chef. It's the case.
I've got something here.
I'll hang up now.
Captain Leng,
we found the suspect vehicle.
Yes.
The camera captured
the suspect dumping the body.
But it was too far away.
And he wore a hat, obscuring his face.
But the license plate number was clear.
Yunxi BH6320.
Alright, I'll look up
the vehicle information.
The owner is Li Dong.
(Lighthouse Night Market)
Are you the owner?
Stop!
- Stop!
What's that?
Move!
Police!
Don't run!
Stop!
It'll hit people.
That's dangerous.
Freeze! Why did you run?
Wait.
Officer,
my arm's about to break. Easy.
Take him away.
Easy.
Arrest her.
She drove into me.
Why are you here?
Why can't I be here?
I just did a heroic act, right?
Instead of thanking me,
you interrogate me?
How lame.
That's not what I meant.
Come on, let's grab a drink.
I'm still on duty.
Next time.
Thanks.
(It's too tight.)
(Do you know Chen Daning?)
(Who?)
Chen Daning from Shipu Village.
I don't know him.
This van is yours, right?
Yeah, it's mine.
Explain this.
Why was your van at the scene
where Chen Daning's body was dumped?
Body was dumped?
Wait. What body?
Behave.
Speak! Why did you kill Chen Daning?
I don't even know who Chen Daning was.
I don't know him at all.
I've never even heard his name before!
What about Xie Wenle?
Xie Wenle?
You mean Xie the idiot, right?
What about him?
He killed someone?
I have absolutely nothing to do
with that.
I'm not close to him at all.
Then tell me what you know.
Well,
Xie the Idiot, no, Xie Wenle.
He lives in Shipu Village.
He renders cooking fat.
He's actually pretty good at it.
Our relationship is purely business.
I just
give him the pork, pig offal, lard,
and that sort of thing I collect.
He renders it into oil for me.
Each time, I leave my van with him.
When it's done, he calls me.
Then I go pick up
both the oil and the van.
That's all I know.
His place has a backyard.
He does all the rendering back there.
Captain Leng.
Over here.
I've seen this bag before.
It's probably been around
since his dad ran the oil mill.
He left it to him.
This is a saw.
I haven't seen this.
Well, I really haven't seen this thing.
I have no idea how he deals
with all the pork and offal.
I've never even been in that backyard.
You have no idea.
Oh my, that smell is unbearable.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
Xie Wenle.
Come out.
Don't arrest me.
Look, I put my gun away.
Come out.
Over there.
Captain Leng.
(Chen Daning's blood
was found on Li Dong's van.)
(We also found his DNA
on the cutting equipment)
(in your basement.)
(Why did you kill Chen Daning?)
What was your connection to him?
Why did you kill him?
Why dismember his body and dump it?
Where is Chen Daning's head?
Answer me, Xie Wenle.
Speak.
Little idiot.
You're ignoring me, huh?
I am your stepdad, after all.
Can't even call me Dad?
You're just like your stupid mom.
A retard.
Give me some money.
No money.
No money?
30,000 yuan. Not much.
Really no money.
Say that again?
I know about that shady business
you people run.
No money?
Who do you think you're fooling?
Get over here.
Come here.
What's with that van outside?
What's going on?
Whose van is it?
My friend's van.
Your friend's van?
A retard like you has a friend?
You have a friend?
It's that short guy's van, right?
He's been coming and going here
so many times.
You think I haven't seen?
You two are making a fortune
off rendering that rotten pork,
aren't you?
Listen up, idiot.
Do you know what this is?
It's illegal. You know that?
Illegal.
If the police find out,
they'll lock you in a dark cell.
Remember?
Just like when your dad
used to lock you in that dark room.
Darker than that.
A drooling idiot like you
will never get out, I'm telling you.
Never get out. Understand?
I'm telling you,
30,000 yuan.
Stupid idiot.
That short guy.
Do you know he's scamming you?
You refine all that oil
for him to sell in the city.
Do you know how much money that makes?
He's taking advantage of you, you idiot.
From now on, let's work together.
To keep the profits
in the family, right?
We'll talk about this later.
Just give me that 30,000 yuan now.
The debt collectors
are breathing down my neck.
No money.
No money?
Is that the only thing
you know how to say?
Don't make me lose my temper.
No money?
Really no money.
You're not giving it to me?
Fine, you stupid idiot.
Think you're all grown up now?
Alright, just you wait.
Tomorrow I'm going to the police
station to report you.
I don't believe I can't deal with you.
Your mother and I are legally married.
We have the marriage certificate.
This house and this yard.
Your mother transferred it all to me.
I took pity on you
and kindly adopted you.
Don't be ungrateful.
Just wait till the police arrest you.
You know what? I'll sell the house
and the yard.
I'll sell all this junk.
I'll make sure you never get out.
Just rot in there.
I'll sell it all.
N-no money.
N-no.
N-no... dark room.
(N-no... dark room.)
Dark room? What dark room?
Dark room.
Xie Wenle,
I don't care
about your reasons or concerns.
Since you're sitting here,
- just...
- No dark room.
No dark room.
(Dark room.)
(No dark room.)
No dark room.
Dark room.
Master.
Send him for psychiatric evaluation.
His arm should be fine.
Do you think he might be faking it?
Fooling us is easy,
but fooling
professional psychiatrists isn't.
If both his parents
had some form of mental illness,
heredity could be a factor.
If that's true,
then his parents' marriage was invalid.
His father found some crazy woman
to marry and have a kid.
It was illegal to begin with.
Frankly, the victim
wasn't exactly a good guy either.
Why else would his own son disown him?
Xie Wenle had it tough.
But murder is illegal, no matter what.
(Remember to get a tetanus shot.)
What a mess.
We never thought this would happen.
- After Xie Hanguo died?
- Totally unexpected.
We didn't hear anything.
- We didn't hear it. We were...
- We didn't hear it.
Captain Leng.
Right over there.
Otherwise, I'd have called the police.
I didn't hear it. I was working.
Master,
I've actually had a question all along.
A victim like Chen Daning
had a terrible reputation
and strained family ties.
To dispose of his body,
Xie Wenle could've buried it
in the mountains or in his own yard.
No one might've found it for years.
But instead, he chopped it to pieces
and dumped it on the highway
without avoiding cameras.
It instantly made it a major case.
That's practically
begging to get caught.
Too many details here don't add up.
But if he truly has a mental illness,
that will actually explain everything.
Thank you.
Captain Leng,
according to villagers
and village officials,
Chen Daning was confirmed
to be an alcoholic and gambler.
After Xie Hanguo's death, he started
harassing Xie Wenle's mother.
He also swindled away
all the savings left by Xie Hanguo
and blew it all.
After Xie Wenle's mother died,
he started harassing Xie Wenle
from time to time.
He was still after money.
Some people even heard him
bragging while drunk,
claiming he'd found a way to get rich
and he could seize the land
from Xie Hanguo's family.
What about Xie Wenle's parents?
Villagers only know she was found
by Xie Hanguo while he was selling oil.
But she did have mental issues.
She rarely spoke.
Sometimes she acted erratically.
Xie Hanguo probably feared
she'd run away,
so he kept her locked in a room.
After Xie Wenle was born,
he finally let her out.
Also, Xie Wenle was often beaten
and abused by Xie Hanguo as a child.
The same room in their house
held both Xie Wenle's mother
and, later, Xie Wenle.
Because Xie Hanguo thought
Xie Wenle was stupid.
Captain Leng.
Captain Leng,
we found it.
This room?
Yes, the dog alerted.
Definitely human remains here.
This is the dark room
Xie Wenle mentioned?
Right.
Secure the scene.
Wait for the forensic unit.
Yes.
Move out.
Duan, set up a perimeter.
Yes.
(No-Name Diner)
Here.
- Take care.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
- We're off.
Drinks for both of you.
Okay.
Have you finished studying?
And you're already gaming?
Look at Chang. He has
top grades and is still diligent.
Go do your homework.
Okay.
Hush now, little one.
Need anything else?
Sorry.
We haven't seen this place so lively
for a while.
Let me feed you. Here.
Come on.
Later, we'll go...
Enjoy.
But the food now
isn't as good as
that made by the last chef.
Try it.
Be grateful there's food.
Stop being picky.
How's your injury healing?
Fine now.
Be more careful next time.
Don't charge recklessly
regardless of their weapons.
Have some broccoli.
Master.
Since Xie Wenle's diagnosed
with limited mental capacity,
regarding sentencing...
There's nothing more we can do.
The rest depends
on the prosecutor's office.
(No-Name Diner)
Hello?
Is our son asleep?
I just wanted to talk to him.
If he's asleep, don't wake him.
I didn't get to spend much time
with him this visit.
Okay.
Next time I'll make it up to him.
Take care of yourself too.
Okay.
Bye.
Master, I'm heading out first.
Are you free later?
Why?
Let's go to...
Okay.
(Strict Discipline)
Guns are our weapons against crime
and our last line of defense
in life-threatening situations.
This mission is exceptionally dangerous.
Stay safe out there.
Why alone? Where's your master?
In a meeting.
The Sishui River
sees drownings every year
from illegal swimming.
No amount of warning signs helps.
But she was wearing jeans.
Unlikely she came to swim.
What do we know?
The victim is a young female.
Based on physical development,
the estimated age is around 25.
Swabbing the mouth and nose
comes back with heavy silt.
I thought she was still breathing
upon entering the water,
meaning ante-mortem drowning.
But after carefully examining her body,
I found a fatal injury on her head.
It was a wound caused by violent impact.
Therefore, homicide is a possibility.
If the body was dumped after death
and the victim stopped breathing
before entering the water,
she couldn't have inhaled silt.
But there's one exception,
passive respiration in water.
She might have been sucked in
by a sand dredger's suction pipe,
and the body's chest cavity
was compressed underwater,
causing the victim
to passively inhale silt.
Ye,
contact our field officers
to investigate.
and find a sand dredger
that's been operating nearby
in the past few days.
Sand dredging has long been banned
on the Sishui River.
- There are still sand dredgers?
- Yeah.
My dad's really into night fishing.
I hear him complain every day.
He says those dredgers rumble all night,
scaring all the fish away.
Doesn't maritime control handle that?
They do.
My dad and his fishing buddies
have reported them countless times.
But the ships now are all modified.
They're fast
and highly elusive.
It's like playing whack-a-mole.
I just remembered.
His fishing buddies
are more into reporting the dredgers
than into fishing.
They share tips daily in a group chat.
I'll ask my dad later
to see if anyone's photographed
that dredger recently.
Any news from your dad?
Not yet.
But he's asked his fishing buddies.
Any moment now.
What's for lunch?
Whatever.
Whatever? Fine.
Please accept this banner.
We really can't accept it.
It's just our duty.
This is my small token of appreciation.
Please take it.
Solutions for the people.
Service with a heart.
That's the duty of the police.
We can't accept it.
Thank you.
But why won't you take it?
Why can't you accept the banner?
Is there something wrong
with these words?
No, right?
No.
They're facts, right?
If it weren't for your keen observation,
could the case be solved?
Wu Da framed me.
And you solved the case
and brought justice for Xiaole.
So I feel I should express something.
Please accept it, okay?
You're too kind.
Really, no need.
Oh my.
He's here to present
a commendation banner?
I know my spying was wrong.
Rest assured.
I will never do such a thing again.
No conscience.
Please accept this small token.
It was a joint effort
by field officers and the forensic unit.
Now the gratitude
only goes to you field officers?
Never mind.
We're noble
and willing to be unsung heroes.
Say that in front of my master.
Reformed ones mean good people.
Take it back.
Alright.
(Dan Qing)
Thank you.
Everyone, disperse.
Enjoy your meal.
Thanks.
This way, please.
You're welcome.
Sorry, I'm late.
No problem, I just got here too.
What's the sudden lunch about?
I wanted to see you.
It was heroic of you last time.
I haven't had a chance to thank you yet.
Do you remember
what you said to me before?
What did I say?
You said you'd always stand
on the side of the light.
You still remember that?
Come on.
To you.
I don't drink. Thanks.
A little red wine won't get you drunk.
To our wonderful reunion.
You're looking a bit tipsy there.
Need a ride?
No, I've called a cab.
Alright. I'll head out first then.
Let's meet up again soon.
Can he endure this physically?
♪Replacing the weight of tears
with that of sweat♪
♪Covering the gunshot's sound
with wounds♪
♪No one is born unyielding and strong♪
♪But because someone
always rushes ahead♪
♪To shield us from the storm♪
♪When every extraordinary act
becomes routine♪
♪Just to polish the badge
upon their shoulder♪
♪Like light surging unseen
through the night♪
♪Converging into your form♪
♪Looking up♪
♪Such dazzling glory♪
♪Like hope♪
♪Reaching out its arms♪
♪Cloaked in light♪
♪Alone, they charge ahead♪
♪Traversing♪
♪The battlefield of fate♪