=The Truth=
=Episode 7=
When we questioned Wu Da,
he admitted he was unwilling
to divorce Wang Xiaole
and he was unhappy
with her dating a new boyfriend.
By the way,
after they got married, they bought
the place at Shancheng Community.
After the divorce,
Wu Da gave it to Wang Xiaole.
Therefore, we believe
there's potential motivation
from a financial perspective.
But the crime scene investigation
shows no definitive evidence
of Wu Da's involvement.
At 10 PM on the night of the murder,
after Wu Da left through the north gate,
he never reappeared on surveillance.
What size shoes does Wu Da wear?
Size 42.
Xiaole called me that night
and asked me to come see her.
I arrived around 9 PM.
Xiaole?
Xiao...
(You and Wang Xiaole are divorced.)
Why keep this relationship?
Xiaole and I never intended to divorce.
Our relationship was great.
But her parents threatened suicide
to force her to divorce me.
It's my fault too,
a man with no money or future.
(I didn't become a doctor.)
Later, I became a pharmaceutical rep
at a bad time
and lost a lot of money.
I couldn't provide Xiaole
a better material life.
That's why I voluntarily
gave her the place.
Although divorced,
we didn't cut ties.
We'd meet two or three times a month,
usually at hotels,
occasionally at home.
No overnight stay.
Xiaole's parents have keys.
If they caught us...
We hadn't met in the last six months.
All we had were texts
and calls.
I knew her parents had introduced her
to someone new.
Huang Chong?
Huang Chong outperforms me in every way.
Xiaole told me they got along well.
It was serious, leading to marriage.
After you had sexual intercourse
with Wang Xiaole that night,
what did you do next?
She took a full shower.
I just took a quick one.
You're beautiful.
Any food? I'm hungry.
I'm getting married.
To that Huang Chong guy?
What does your family see in him?
He's permanent staff.
And he's reliable.
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
Wontons are in the kitchen.
I'll heat them for you.
No need.
I'm leaving.
(You left?)
What was the exact time?
10 PM.
Where did you go after leaving?
I didn't go home after leaving.
I just drank by the roadside.
Where'd you buy it?
A small supermarket there.
Then what?
After that,
I... I knew
Xiaole was marrying another man.
I was mentally prepared,
but I couldn't accept it emotionally.
I hadn't even finished half of it
before getting drunk.
The cool breeze later sobered me up.
So I went home.
What time was that approximately?
I really don't remember.
I was already drunk then.
Where exactly were you drinking?
The specific spot?
Left of the community's north gate,
there's a large flower bed.
From our place...
From Xiaole's place, you could see it.
Captain Leng.
I heard Wu Da and Wang Xiaole
stole their household registries
to marry
due to family opposition.
They clearly loved each other.
Why couldn't they stay together?
Life's pressures, I suppose.
What would you two like to order?
Sir, got a minute?
Did you see this person
on the night of the 9th?
This person? No.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Why are you asking
about that drunkard again?
Didn't you ask the other day?
He comes often.
Every time, he buys a bottle of liquor.
The cheapest kind.
After buying it,
he drinks by that flower bed over there.
That one right there.
He can't hold his liquor,
and he's a mean drunk.
Whenever he drinks, he makes a scene.
Sometimes he cries.
Sometimes he howls over there.
It's terrible.
I heard the woman who died
in our neighborhood was his ex-wife.
Did he do it?
Will a death here
affect the housing prices?
Did he come the night of the 9th?
He did.
Bought a bottle of liquor and left.
Do you remember what time he left?
What time?
Around after 10 PM, I think.
There were still many customers then.
Where did he go after leaving?
Did you see?
I saw him.
He went out, turned left,
and headed straight for that flower bed.
Definitely that flower bed.
It's him.
Every night when I walk my dog here,
I see him.
Drunk out of his mind.
Even my dog wants to avoid him.
You mean the 9th?
He was there that day too.
I remember it clearly.
Sir,
do you remember about what time
you saw him?
I walk my dog at fixed times every day.
Come rain or shine.
Twice a day.
One walk is at this time of day.
The other is at night.
I went out at 11:30 PM
and returned at 1:50 AM.
Both when I left and returned,
I saw him. He slumped here.
Are you sure it's him?
The lighting around here
isn't great at night.
Could it be that you...
Young man,
are you saying I'm old
and my eyes are failing?
It was absolutely him.
It's not like I've seen him
just once or twice.
He's here every few days.
A troubled young man, hooked on drink.
It's disgraceful.
Right.
I even want to teach him a lesson.
Let me tell you.
These young people today...
How should I put it?
Yeah.
Back in our day, right?
We came home right after work.
(North Gate)
Based on our neighborhood canvass,
Wu Da was drinking at the north gate
flower bed during the crime's timeframe.
He couldn't have killed her.
Time to eat!
Focus on identifying this person
in the surveillance.
Come on, eat first.
Come on, let's eat.
I'll get yours, Master.
Thank you.
Here, help yourselves.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Here.
Alright.
Okay, the chopsticks.
Ziwu.
Perfect timing. Join us.
Captain Leng,
I found small debris on the doormat
at Wang Xiaole's place earlier.
Tests revealed
it was fresh Masson pine bark.
North of Shancheng Community
is a large pine forest.
Neither Wu Da nor the victim's parents
have hiking habits.
The chance of them
stepping on it is very low.
And it's mostly Japanese red pine,
Chinese red pine, and Armand pine here.
Masson pines are very rare.
Especially in the urban area.
Alright, hurry up and eat.
After eating, we'll check the woods
near the victim's place.
Captain Sun,
we've been here for days now.
Why has Captain Leng
been wearing sunglasses all the time?
Look at you, Zhou.
What's with all the questions?
Captain Leng's eyes
were injured during a mission.
He avoids light.
That's why
he has to wear glasses day and night.
But they're not sunglasses.
They don't block his view.
So, you...
Captain Leng.
We got something.
The packaging colors
of these condoms are all different.
They weren't tossed on the same day.
Here too.
Come look at this.
There's a telescope here.
It offers a clear view
into the victim's bedroom.
No valuable fingerprints found
on the packaging of these four condoms.
The user was likely wearing gloves
when handling them.
I found latex and talcum powder traces
on the tree bark.
Consistent with medical gloves.
So I conclude
that the suspect
climbed the tree wearing gloves.
Specifically, medical latex gloves.
That matches Ye's earlier theory.
The suspect is meticulous, organized,
and highly cautious.
Given those traits, the medical gloves,
and the skill with a scalpel,
it's highly likely the suspect
has a medical background.
He may also have hobbies
like hiking or rock climbing.
But both Wang Xiaole and Wu Da
graduated from medical school.
And they both worked in related fields.
Within their social circles,
many are doctors
or have medical backgrounds.
I think that scope is still too broad.
Alright.
You've paid respects to my parents.
I know you don't stand on ceremony,
but this outfit
is a bit much.
(Beloved Father Chen Yiqing's Tomb
Beloved Mother Liu Rongdan's Tomb)
They are always in my heart.
The rest is just formality.
It's for the living to see.
Besides,
I need to stand out.
So they don't lose track of me.
Let's go.
No word from Bao Hei
these past few days.
Probably busy digging graves.
Once we get past this hurdle,
we'll meet Bao Hei, right?
Hard to say.
Bao Hei has a reputation
for his cold heart and cruel hands.
Earning his real trust won't be easy.
Trust from someone like him? Forget it.
To get him to cooperate,
we need to intimidate him.
Plainly speaking,
we're not the only source around
these days.
But an ex-boyfriend
who's an active-duty cop
is not something
just anyone can produce.
Are you sure?
Should you reconsider?
Dragging this out with Bao Hei
benefits no one.
Besides, he started this whole thing.
We can't avoid it.
If we avoid it,
he'll only get more suspicious.
We might as well go with the flow
and let Bao Hei see
what we're capable of.
You hate him that much?
Not running into him
all these years was fine.
But fate brought us together.
Well,
how could I possibly
let him get away easily
and live so happily?
(Sexual Wellness Products)
Check up ahead.
Okay.
Do you have this product here?
This one isn't currently sold here.
It's one
of those free contraceptive supplies.
No, we don't have this one here.
From what I know,
it's not available nearby.
Thank you.
Master,
the pharmacy staff
said this condom isn't for sale.
It's handed out freely across the city.
Mainly at county or district
family planning departments,
hospitals, and neighborhood committees.
In that case,
we can trace the source
and look into its distribution process.
Find out which communities
and streets are involved
and target
units or individuals
connected to Wang Xiaole and Wu Da.
Okay.
Ye Qian?
Shopping?
No.
I'm on a case.
Yumo.
I didn't expect you
to become a police officer.
Yumo, I...
After that incident, I changed my name.
The old Chen Yumo is gone.
Let's start over.
My name is Dan Qing now.
When did you come back to Yunxi?
I returned several years ago.
I've been looking for you all along.
My ride is here.
Need a lift?
No, thanks.
Are you sure?
I'll head out then.
Let's exchange WeChat.
To keep in touch.
Okay.
See you around.
Your ex-boyfriend keeps staring at us.
(The old Chen Yumo is gone.)
(Let's start over.)
(My name is Dan Qing now.)
(Ye Qian and Yumo)
♪Do your best and don't let go♪
Ye Qian.
I like both our names.
Ye Qian and Yumo.
♪All the rights and wrongs
will fade away♪
♪I really want to know
where you landed later♪
♪So many words I've wanted to say♪
Ye Qian.
When will you paint
that painting you promised me?
Don't worry. I'm working on it.
Then when will you give it to me?
Tomorrow, the day after,
or the day after that?
I'm warning you now.
If you break your promise,
I'll never talk to you again.
Then I'll keep painting for you forever.
Until I can't hold a brush.
That's the Ye Qian I like.
♪Can you feel me this way♪
What did you say?
Say it again.
I didn't say anything.
I said you're wonderful.
What did you say?
Say it again.
I didn't say anything.
♪Time never lingers for love's sake♪
♪But the world's complexity won't break♪
♪I pray love's course remains true♪
♪Wherever you are,
may happiness find you♪
♪Remember this♪
Are you busy?
Look up someone for me.
The name's Dan Qing.
Sending it now.
Okay, thanks.
Where did the bloody clothes go?
The scene was covered in blood.
But no blood on the clothes?
That's impossible.
What is it, Long?
That telescope
is the most common basic model.
No fingerprints.
No DNA, nothing at all.
We can only tell
it's been there a long time.
The victim bought the resale property
when marrying four years ago.
The suspect's been watching the victim
that long?
If that's the case,
we can exclude who Wang Xiaole and Wu Da
met in the last four years, right?
No fingerprints besides those of Wu Da,
Wang Xiaole, Huang Chong,
or the victim's parents
are found at the scene.
DNA
suggests the killer
didn't have time to clean yet.
(Wu Da)
I won't finish early today.
Don't wait for me.
By the way,
I ordered some vegetable racks online.
Should arrive in a few days.
They've arrived?
Don't open them yet.
The screws inside are sharp.
I'll install them on the wall
when I'm home.
That's Captain Leng calling.
Must be work.
I need to go.
(Forensic Imagery Room)
Captain Leng,
I found no valuable clues
at the south gate.
Right.
Same for the woods
outside the north gate.
Too little useful evidence.
I'm still looking.
(Yunxi Medical University)
Ye,
sorry to keep you waiting.
(File Bag)
Look, these old files
are stored
in the old teaching building's archive.
We haven't digitized them yet.
Hence the delay.
You're too kind, Mr. Liu.
I should thank you
for assisting our investigation.
(Graduate Registration Form)
My pleasure.
You may not know.
I was Wu Da and Xiaole's
homeroom teacher.
When Wu Da applied
to transfer departments,
(Wu Da's Profile)
I advised him not to act impulsively.
Ours is a top university.
Getting into our department isn't easy.
I advised him
to cherish this opportunity.
But he refused on the spot.
He even said he wasn't cut out
for medicine at all,
and Xiaole was the only reason
he chose clinical.
- That kid...
- Sir,
based on your understanding of Wu Da,
could he achieve such precision
with the incision?
Wu Da?
He couldn't hold the scalpel properly
during training.
This photo
shows a clean, neat incision
with perfectly even force.
Without years of practice
and solid fundamentals,
one simply couldn't have done it.
Sir,
Wu Da received a disciplinary demerit
while at school?
It was for fighting
with another student.
The kids acted impulsively,
but actually,
they were very close friends.
They were inseparable all day long.
Ye,
how are your parents doing overseas?
They're doing fine.
When you talk to them next time,
tell them
we old friends still think of them.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
By the way,
could you please help me find out
the specific details
of Wu Da's fight and demerit?
No problem. I'll tell you
as soon as I find anything.
Thank you.
Take care. I'm off.
Alright, take care.
I went to a movie
with Little Zhao that day.
But I used your name to invite her.
You don't mind, do you?
Can't you rely on yourself?
I do want to rely on myself, bro.
But I can't get her out like that.
She won't come.
Just tell me,
is there even the slightest chance
between you two?
There isn't.
Okay then, that puts my mind at ease.
Actually, the atmosphere
during the movie was pretty good.
It looked promising.
But unfortunately,
I had to leave halfway through.
How about doing another favor for me?
What now?
I invited Little Zhao
for a late-night snack.
I said you'll go too.
And she just replied, saying yes.
(No-Name Diner)
Jing.
You're here. Perfect, it's all ready.
Great.
Dig in.
- Thanks.
- Jing.
Here, Little Zhao.
Is she your girlfriend?
A friend.
- No.
- Not my girlfriend.
- Sit.
- Eat up.
Holler if you need me.
Got it.
So this is the amazing restaurant
you keep mentioning?
The place looks pretty ordinary.
And the dishes
seem like regular home cooking.
Let me try this.
That's delicious.
I think it's quite tasty.
Better than my cooking.
It's good.
If you say it's good, then it is.
Tasty.
Captain Qin, you're here.
Is it ready?
All ready.
Come on in and sit down.
I'll serve the noodles right away.
Just sit.
- Okay.
- Right away.
- Jing.
- Come on.
What's going on?
Serve the noodles, Shan.
Qian.
Long.
Serve the noodles.
Long, you're here too.
You're here.
Enjoy.
Qian and Long, you're here too.
- You're here.
- You must be starving.
Eat your food.
Here.
- Free noodles.
- Qian. Long.
Come on.
Everyone, eat up.
- Noodles.
- Serve this table.
Here.
Coming right up.
Give this to them first.
How about we find another place?
What's wrong?
I feel creeped out even though
I haven't done anything wrong.
It's no big deal.
They're the Public Order Unit.
The power of justice.
There must be another operation tonight.
There's an operation?
(Team One, Team One.)
(Team Two, Team Two, move out.)
Copy. Moving out.
- Copy that.
- Move.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
What's happening tonight?
Why the rush?
Liu and Shan, come here.
Clean those up.
They probably won't be back soon.
Grab that bucket.
Pour everything into the bucket
for the stray cats, dogs, and such.
Look at them.
Put it on the table for now.
- Hello, Master.
- Hello, Lei.
Coming.
(No-Name Diner)
What's going on tonight?
Just sit.
You'll get used to it.
That's the nature of their job.
They leave at a moment's notice.
How about I join you?
Or it'll all go to waste.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Ms. Jing,
does Ye Qian come here often?
He comes often.
Has he brought other girls here before?
Anyway, you're the first girl
they've brought here.
Ms. Jing,
is your family in the same line of work?
My husband, Jiao Lei,
is their colleague.
He's also a cop.
My son used to be a soldier.
A border guard.
That's cool.
Quite a handsome young man.
Lots of girls liked him.
But he died on duty five years ago.
I've worked in food service
since before my son.
I wanted to open my own restaurant
to honor my son
and keep myself occupied.
Jiao's unit was setting up a canteen
for field personnel back then,
and the leaders sympathized with me,
so they gave us priority
and hence this restaurant.
We sometimes provide meals
for sanitation workers.
It's volunteer-based too.
People need something to hold onto.
It feels good to do something
for that purpose.
Can I come help next time then?
Of course.
You're welcome.
Alright.
Eat more.
You eat too.
Slow down.
Is this the old chemical factory's
discharge pool?
Why the strong smell?
This whole area
used to be a chemical factory.
Later, the factory relocated.
The land was sold.
It's been left abandoned ever since.
Now it's entirely a garbage dump.
If it hadn't become a dump,
I wouldn't have found this place.
See that surveillance camera?
Coming through the woods,
there's only this one camera.
The camera was installed
by the city sanitation department
to catch trucks illegally dumping trash.
Didn't expect it
to help us out big time.
Is the person
who threw something into the pond
the same one who appeared
at the south gate of the community?
Looks like it.
But the camera's resolution is lacking.
We need to analyze it thoroughly.
Found it.
♪Replacing the weight of tears
with that of sweat♪
♪Covering the gunshot's sound
with wounds♪
♪No one is born unyielding and strong♪
♪But because someone
always rushes ahead♪
♪To shield us from the storm♪
♪When every extraordinary act
becomes routine♪
♪Just to polish the badge
upon their shoulder♪
♪Like light surging unseen
through the night♪
♪Converging into your form♪
♪Looking up♪
♪Such dazzling glory♪
♪Like hope♪
♪Reaching out its arms♪
♪Cloaked in light♪
♪Alone, they charge ahead♪
♪Traversing♪
♪The battlefield of fate♪