=The Truth=
=Episode 8=
Can we extract DNA?
Waiting for the results.
If we can confirm
these hairs belong to the victim,
then the owner of these clothes
is the real killer.
You're staying here all night,
leaving your dad alone?
Ms. Wang's with him.
Have you eaten?
Bread's over there.
Have some.
Otherwise, your stomach will hurt.
I ate.
I'll go to Jiao.
Any new clues?
Master.
Sit.
Judging from this video,
these two individuals have
very similar builds and clothing.
The bag he's carrying
is basically identical to the one
we fished out of the lake.
So we can conclude
they're the same person.
If they're the same person,
then this person exited the south gate
of the community at 1:05 AM,
and reached the pond by 1:15 AM.
That's several kilometers away.
He was quite quick.
After dumping the bag,
where did he go?
(South gate, Pond)
Qian.
(Yumo, long time no see)
(Dan Qing, long time no see)
(Dan Qing, long time no see.
Available this weekend?)
He took the bait already?
Seems he still can't forget you.
Right?
Bao Hei will definitely
send people to watch.
Let's hope your ex-boyfriend is smart.
I don't care.
As long as he takes the bait,
he can't escape.
(Yunxi Police Department)
The blood
(Hauled up: Sports jacket, scalpel, etc.)
on the gloves and on the scalpel
are confirmed to belong
to the victim, Wang Xiaole.
On the sports jacket,
I detected two different DNAs.
One belongs to the victim Wang Xiaole,
the other is from an unknown male.
I found some hairs
on the zipper of the sports jacket.
Testing confirmed they also
belong to the victim Wang Xiaole.
Based on the location, I speculate
when the killer
(Hauled up: Key, rubber gloves, etc.)
grabbed Wang Xiaole's hair,
he tore it out during repeated impacts.
So we can be fairly certain
this unknown male is the killer.
Can we find this person using the DNA?
I've already uploaded the data.
If this person has a previous record
in our system,
then we'll find him quickly.
But if not,
then I can only run a comparison
after we apprehend a suspect.
But we can confirm it's not Wu Da.
This key appears to be a duplicate.
Does it open
the victim's apartment door?
We've tried, Captain Leng.
It does open.
That bag looks like the giveaway
for signing up for a gym membership.
If there's a brand on the bag,
we could trace it.
That gym went out of business years ago.
Long, go sleep in my room.
No prints on that thing.
He wore gloves.
Young people can sleep soundly.
I really envy him.
I have some findings on the video.
(Dongyuan, Alley 07)
But it can't be enlarged any further.
This is the best it gets.
Now we know the person is
in medium build, on the thin side.
Estimated height
between 1.75m and 1.80m.
He was heading towards Dongyuan.
Dongyuan is an urban village.
The permanent population
might be at least 3,000.
Oh, no.
That's just permanent population.
Including migrant population,
it would be more.
That's much more.
The roads and terrain
in Dongyuan are complex.
There are only about
seven or eight cameras total.
Too many blind spots.
If he is a resident of Dongyuan,
that would be manageable.
If he just passed through
Dongyuan or hid there
briefly before leaving,
that makes it tricky.
I'll say something.
We currently know the suspect
had been peeking at the victim
for years from the pine woods
behind Shancheng Community.
That shows he's quite familiar
with the surrounding terrain.
West of Shancheng Community,
less than 500 meters away
(Map)
is the Ring Road.
The traffic there is very convenient.
He could discard the clothes
along the way.
The suspect left Shancheng Community
after the crime
without drawing attention.
So I don't think he would
deliberately take a detour
to Dongyuan in the opposite direction.
That'd also increase the risk
of being spotted and noticed.
I think even if the suspect isn't
a permanent resident of Dongyuan,
he at least frequents this area.
Captain Leng, I think
if we take action
in the Dongyuan jurisdiction now,
we might alert the suspect
and he might flee?
Our operation to dredge the sewage pond
was quite a scene.
If the suspect was watching
from the shadows,
he must have alerted by now.
Otherwise, to be safe,
we'll first coordinate with
the community security unit,
and conduct a sweep under the pretext
of preventing robbery and theft.
Start with the permanent residents.
You, Wang Tong.
Here!
Liu Yang.
Based on the social circles
of Wu Da and Wang Xiaole,
you conduct an investigation
to see if anyone has connections
to the Dongyuan area.
Action! Hurry!
- Yes!
This is the Dongyuan urban village.
Let's go take a look.
Alright.
This way.
Who's the owner?
Me! I'm the owner.
Ask you something.
We're from CID.
Okay.
Ma'am.
Yes?
Ask you something.
What is it?
Are your customers all regulars?
- Any unfamiliar faces?
- Yes.
All residents from nearby.
All residents?
Yes.
No strangers?
No.
Just ahead.
Thank you.
Okay, no problem.
This one's ready.
Hurry.
Okay. Come on.
Have one.
I'm not hungry.
Take it easy.
How long have you been a policeman?
Four years.
Four years?
Well, I...
I became a policeman at twenty.
I'll be retiring soon.
I wanted to go all out
on this Shancheng case.
But I'm old now, not capable as before.
Can't keep up
with you young folks anymore.
What flavor?
Ms. Wang.
You're back.
Dinner's kept warm for you.
Go wash your hands and eat.
Dad.
Leng.
I won't wash these dishes
of yours today, okay?
Well, you got off work early.
I want to go back early today.
My daughter brought the kids over
and they're staying
at my place for a few days.
Alright. Thank you.
Leng, well...
I've worked for you
for years now, right?
Well, we know each other pretty well.
You know how expensive
everything is nowadays.
I have elderly and kids to support.
- I need to...
- Ms. Wang.
Ms. Wang, I understand.
My dad can't be left alone.
Well, I'll give you
an extra 800 yuan a month.
What do you think?
That's too much.
Thank you.
My job is really demanding.
You really helped me a lot.
No problem.
Then it's settled.
Okay.
I-I'm leaving then.
Alright. Take care.
I saw it online.
Didn't expect
he's running an art gallery now.
(Phone password)
Okay, see you then.
Who's it?
Who are you meeting then?
None of your business.
Is it your unrequited love?
How's it going? Tell me.
You're wearing this tomorrow?
What's wrong?
It's nice. Suits you.
Good taste.
Master.
New info from the medical school.
They found the guy who got into
a fight with Wu Da during school.
He is Niu Bosheng,
male, 34 years old,
a local.
Ph.D. in Clinical Medicine
from Yunxi Medical University.
They were in the same year at college,
but in different classes.
He attended the same middle school
and high school as Wang Xiaole.
He joined the mountaineering club
in college.
After graduation, he worked
in General Surgery at Central Hospital.
Under the counterpart support policy,
he holds clinic hours every Wednesday
at Dongyuan Community Health Center.
Wu Da got into a physical fight
with him during school.
They got a demerit for it.
So why did they fight?
Wu Da accused Niu Bosheng
of peeking and harassing Wang Xiaole.
(Yunxi Central Hospital)
You did it on purpose?
Didn't we agree not to wear it together?
I swear on my life, man.
I was sleeping when you got up.
How did I know you'd wear this?
If you can't stand it,
there's a clothing store.
Go buy a new one.
Why don't you buy one?
First, this isn't my fault.
You should've told me last night.
Second, I'm broke.
It's field work today.
Why are you coming along?
Your master said
that person is basically
a high-IQ criminal.
You might need help, so he sent me.
Don't reveal who we are at first.
Just talk to him.
See how he reacts.
Of course. Let's go.
That's it?
Yes. Enter the info and hit submit.
That's it.
Okay, thanks.
No problem.
Registered.
You! Stay away from me!
Where can I go? It's crowded here.
I wish to stay away from you.
Way too crowded.
All hospitals are like this, crowded.
Definitely.
(Patient 047, Si Yuanlong,
please proceed to Room 1.)
Let's go.
Which one of you is the patient?
Me. He's just here with me.
A grown man needs company
to see the doctor?
I'm emotionally fragile.
What's the problem?
My hand hurts.
The wound's healing okay.
Scar tissue doesn't look hypertrophic.
How did this happen?
Well...
It...
He got drunk and rowdy with me.
He even pulled a knife
and said I stole his girlfriend.
Tell me, is he crazy?
Listen up!
I want all of it covered,
the medical bills,
the trauma, everything!
Why should I pay? Not a chance!
You kept texting my girlfriend,
like a ghost haunting me.
Yet you want me to pay your bills?
Wanting a beating?
Me? You're insane!
You always pester her.
It's one-sided love. You know?
Your girlfriend? You...
You...
You two, go out if you want to quarrel.
This is a hospital.
I'll prescribe you
erythromycin ointment.
Apply it for several days.
Okay.
Alright.
Anything else?
What's going on?
Sorry, Doctor.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
W-Wear the mask.
Okay. Thank you.
We'll go get the medicine.
Go get it.
Thank you.
Hello.
Captain Leng, we have the results.
It matches the male DNA
on that sports jacket.
Thank you for your hard work.
Tell the forensic unit staff
to get off work early.
Okay.
Confirmed.
(Longyan)
- Good!
- Impressive!
Little Qian,
your cooking skills are amazing.
Why not consider being my partner?
You're wrong.
Little Qian is the star
of our police force,
Captain Leng's prized student.
He'll become unit chief,
deputy chief, then chief someday.
Then off to the province, the ministry.
Your small place can't satisfy him.
But it can satisfy me.
You? What can you do?
I can be the fortune cat.
I'm serious.
Quit being a policeman.
It's exhausting and pays poorly.
Think about it.
You won't run off
early again today, right?
No, we definitely won't run off today.
What made you decide to cook here today?
I promised him this before.
Si Yuanlong.
You like me?
Y-Yes.
Haven't I told you
s-several times before?
It's real, not a joke.
Do you still want to be my friend?
I really enjoy being friends with you.
But I don't like you as my boyfriend.
And you, Ye Qian.
I'm telling you. It's unnecessary.
It's my business that I like you.
You don't have to like me,
but don't set me up with anyone.
What do you mean?
Do you look down on me or on him?
I'm not worth your time.
I'm sorry.
Wait. Are you really leaving?
You're just letting him leave?
Leave if you want.
I won't leave.
I'll stay with you.
Sorry.
I was a bit harsh just now.
Don't mind it.
It's fine.
I'm glad that you see me
as a friend. Really.
And I don't have many merits,
but I'm definitely thick-skinned.
Did he get any news
about Chen Yumo recently?
W-Why would you say that?
He's been in a good mood lately.
He never apologizes to me
if he's in a bad mood.
Well, he does have an appointment later.
Probably with his unrequited love.
But I don't know the details.
I just overheard them
chatting on WeChat.
Do you know where they're going?
To a place called Niu something...
Probably a gallery run
by one of your friends?
Come on. Let's go see the show.
It's inappropriate.
Coming or not?
If not, I'll go alone.
Yes.
If you go, I'll go.
Name.
Niu Bosheng.
Do you know why you're here?
Xiaole is dead.
You would definitely find me.
Tell us.
What did you do to Wang Xiaole?
I set up a telescope in the woods
north of her community.
You call that peeping.
So why were you peeping at Wang Xiaole?
I love her.
That's all?
That's all.
(Modern Art Exhibition)
Little Qian looks quite decent now.
Why doesn't he just put on makeup?
This is almost like wearing makeup.
Right. About that thing, don't...
Let's not mention that.
Okay.
Besides, we don't suit.
From family background
to interests to careers.
And you're a policeman.
If I weren't a policeman,
would I have a chance?
I'm joking. Don't be so shocked.
I know we're not from the same world.
Why did you become a policeman?
I talked about this
with Little Qian before.
My parents
always hoped I'd find an easier job.
But being a policeman
is anything but easy.
It's really exhausting,
with no fixed holidays
or high pay.
Just look how broke I am.
But later, I thought it over.
Becoming a policeman
is absolutely the best choice
I've made in over 20 years.
The sense of achievement
from cracking a case
with some clues
is something no amount
of money can ever buy.
Get him to talk about
that fight with Wu Da
in med school that got him demerits.
Talk.
That's because Wu Da
caught me peeking at Xiaole.
He even suspected
I had an affair with Xiaole.
Then we got into a fight.
But at least that day,
Xiaole finally knew about me.
Honestly, I never meant
to disrupt their lives.
I just wanted to watch over her quietly.
At first, Wu Da seemed like
a decent boyfriend.
He treated Xiaole well,
and seemed faithful.
But he just couldn't make it big.
He couldn't even hold a scalpel steady,
so he couldn't become a doctor.
Seeing all those pharmaceutical reps
making big money,
he can barely scrape by.
But poor Xiaole suffered,
living in such a remote place.
Actually, he didn't buy
that second-hand apartment himself.
(Wedding of Wu Da and Wang Xiaole)
Is this the place?
Welcome!
Congrats!
- Happy wedding!
Come on in.
Okay.
Did Wu Da borrow money from you?
Yes.
He asked every classmate
from high school.
Did you lend him?
It was a huge amount.
How could I possibly lend him?
Besides,
he even needs to borrow money
to buy that second-hand apartment
in Shancheng Community.
He's really hit rock bottom.
He asked me
and I didn't know what to do.
You know?
Don't lend him.
Why would Wu Da even invite you
to his wedding with Wang Xiaole?
Wouldn't it be awkward
seeing each other?
Their wedding was just Wu Da's scheme
to rake in cash gifts.
He sent invitations to everyone,
friends or strangers.
Lots of people showed up.
Actually, we didn't even greet.
But I loved Xiaole.
I can't stand seeing
Xiaole suffer like this.
I took out 200,000 yuan myself.
I got a classmate to lend it
to Wu Da in his name.
Then what?
You asked the hospital leadership
to take on the task at the Dongyuan
Community Health Center, right?
Just to get closer
to Wang Xiaole, right?
Right?
Right.
I didn't want to be too far from Xiaole.
I don't trust Wu Da.
He's too useless.
Don't trust him?
So you went to peek at her
and did that disgusting thing
up in a tree?
I love Xiaole.
I truly love Xiaole.
I haven't touched any woman
besides Xiaole.
But I... But I am a normal man.
Right? I have desires too.
Like Nabokov said,
Xiaole is my life's light,
my desire's fire.
She is my goddess,
my soul,
and also my sin.
You're so shameless.
This isn't about shame.
It's beyond morality.
This is love.
Because I truly love her.
Xiaole was shining to me,
making everything else in the world dim.
All I can do is,
silently,
secretly,
far away in a corner, to watch over her,
bless her,
and love her.
It's been so long.
She's late, right?
If I were Chen Yumo,
I'll just stand him up.
Stand him up. Please.
If I were meeting you, I'd be early.
We're waiting anyway.
Let's make a bet.
You learned some bad tricks.
Bet on what?
Bet on whether his crush shows up.
I bet she comes.
Then I bet she doesn't come.
Fine. If you lose,
promise me one thing.
If I lose,
I'll do whatever you say.
Deal.
Ye Qian.
You got here early?
You weren't here when I arrived,
so I came in first.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
M-My fault.
I jinxed it.
I'll go buy you qingbuliang.
No.
A bet's a bet.
Just to be clear.
I can't be your girlfriend.
Relax. It's definitely not that.
I'll go buy you qingbuliang.
Alright.
Let's talk about that.
On the night of the crime,
what were you doing
between 12 AM to 1 AM?
Sleeping at home.
With whom?
By myself.
Where do you live?
Guanlan Court.
Think it over.
No need.
I'm a person with regular habits.
I have clinic hours at the Dongyuan
Health Center every Wednesday
just to go see Xiaole.
The clinic closes at 5 PM,
and she's home by 6 PM.
Then I went to the woods
and watched until 9:30 PM.
I went home after that.
Quite regular.
Take a look.
Yours, right?
Explain it.
About this question... I...
I-I don't know how to answer.
I did own an identical jacket
and the same bag.
But both items were stolen.
Stolen?
Where were they stolen?
Six months ago,
I kept that jacket as a spare
in the locker room
at the Dongyuan Community.
But my locker was pried open
and I couldn't find them.
Some colleagues and the security guards
can prove this.
Since the stolen items weren't valuable,
I didn't report it to the police.
Here. Qingbuliang.
I heard their qingbuliang is delicious.
Try some.
Not in the mood.
What kind of art exhibition?
It takes that long?
In my opinion,
Little Qian finally
got to see his unrequited love.
He must have
a lot of things to talk about
and memories to share.
He must cherish
every single moment with her.
Hey, where are you going?
The night snack is on me.
Wait, I came straight
after work to be with you.
I put in efforts.
Don't be mad.
I'll treat you to late-night snacks.
No. Too angry to eat.
Where are you going?
Going home.
Let me accompany you.
♪Replacing the weight of tears
with that of sweat♪
♪Covering the gunshot's sound
with wounds♪
♪No one is born unyielding and strong♪
♪But because someone
always rushes ahead♪
♪To shield us from the storm♪
♪When every extraordinary act
becomes routine♪
♪Just to polish the badge
upon their shoulder♪
♪Like light surging unseen
through the night♪
♪Converging into your form♪
♪Looking up♪
♪Such dazzling glory♪
♪Like hope♪
♪Reaching out its arms♪
♪Cloaked in light♪
♪Alone, they charge ahead♪
♪Traversing♪
♪The battlefield of fate♪