=The Truth=
=Episode 9=
I remember you loved
Rembrandt most back then.
You always said his paintings
carried a tragic tone.
What about you?
Do you still like Monet?
No, not anymore.
Do you still paint?
And you?
What do you do now?
I don't paint either.
Now,
I run a small business.
Remember how we used to come here
after evening self-study?
Yes.
People say you should look forward.
But some things
just can't be forgotten.
Like this place.
I still remember us sitting
right over there discussing Rembrandt.
This is my favorite painting.
What do you like about Rembrandt?
Some say
Rembrandt's art depicts the struggle
between light and dark.
What do you think?
I agree.
Light and dark
are inherently intertwined.
Just like this world.
There's sunlight, and there are shadows.
That's why I never
really liked Rembrandt.
I prefer Monet,
always standing solely in the sunlight.
How lucky must one be
to always stand in the light.
Let's talk next time.
Dan Qing.
Take care.
You too.
Here, your favorite qingbuliang.
Jing, you dote on me most.
Did you meet the nephew of Tang's wife?
We added on social media,
but haven't met.
Why? What happened?
Nothing to talk about.
What would we talk about?
How could you not know
what to talk about?
Our jobs are completely different.
He's at the Forestry Bureau.
We just don't connect.
So you...
You two should talk
about things outside work.
Like what?
Like movies,
art,
pop songs,
food,
and anything young people like.
Jing, you know how it is.
I barely have time
to pay attention to any of that.
Just making small talk?
I'm really at my wits' end
with you cops.
Well...
For us, it's just the same
three points every day:
the station, home, and here.
The most relaxing part of my day
is eating something at your place.
And the thing we care about most
is solving cases.
Nothing else much.
I can see it now.
Your love life will only be solved
within the police department.
Let me show you something good.
Here.
How is it?
Do you like it?
It smells amazing!
How did you know I hadn't eaten?
What is this you cooked?
What's wrong now?
Weren't you on a date
with your unrequited love today?
How was it? Tell me.
Mind your own business.
You're in a bad mood.
Something's bothering you. Talk to me.
Won't say?
Then I'm going to eat noodles.
(Dongyuan Community
Convenience Health Service Station)
I never expected
that Niu Bosheng really lost
his bag and clothes.
This guy is so twisted.
He must have planned it long ago.
That's possible.
But getting people who barely know him
to remember something from months ago
was still quite risky, wasn't it?
Captain Sun.
Why are you speaking up for Niu Bosheng?
You know you had a dream last night?
Dream talk.
What did I say?
What could it be?
Just kept saying one person's name.
Yumo.
It is all Wang Xiaole.
There are words too.
May 17, 2005.
School organized spring outing.
This is the first photo
I took of Xiaole.
Xiaole looks beautiful.
Like an angel.
December 30, 2006.
New Year's Gala.
Xiaole's singing was so beautiful.
June 2008.
Grade-wide group photo.
What a pity.
Our class wasn't next to Xiaole's class.
That's so corny.
This guy is really lovesick.
These photos
are arranged chronologically.
No close-ups, all taken secretly.
Condoms of the same brand.
Round packaging.
Also arranged chronologically.
But why are all the wrappers
under the tree square?
The packaging of these condoms
is of different colors.
They weren't tossed on the same day.
This type of condom
shouldn't be commercially available.
They should be
free family planning supplies.
Officer,
I suggest you ask the family planning,
neighborhood committee, and hospitals.
(Mutt)
I've already told you.
I didn't kill Xiaole.
You don't need to waste your time on me.
Why don't you go find the real killer?
Niu Bosheng,
you're an educated person.
You should understand
that we wouldn't have brought you here
without solid evidence.
Put it this way.
The evidence we have
points overwhelmingly to you.
The reason we're still
talking to you here
is to give you a chance to confess.
In my lifetime,
I dare to admit what I do.
I'll never shirk it.
But for things I didn't do,
whether it's here,
the procuratorate, or the court,
I won't admit.
Because I didn't do it.
How long have you known Wang Xiaole?
17 years.
Did she know you loved her?
No.
You never confessed to her?
I've said it before.
Watching her from afar
was enough for me.
After Xiaole got together with Wu Da,
I gradually realized
that I projected myself onto Wu Da.
When they were together,
it felt like I was with Xiaole.
To be honest,
if you truly love someone,
her happiness becomes your happiness.
Xiaole chose Wu Da.
And I sincerely wished them well.
I hope they'll have a long, happy,
and peaceful marriage.
Then one day, they got divorced.
Honestly, I was pretty down for a while.
But later I figured it out.
Xiaole could find happiness
with Huang Chong.
And she could get rid
of Wu Da, that deadbeat.
Wang Xiaole and Huang Chong
were already planning to get married.
They planned to move downtown
after the wedding.
No more peeping this time, right?
Huang Chong owns
two properties in Yunxi.
The most suitable place for marriage
is the Riverside Garden in downtown.
I rented an apartment
across from their complex.
The location and view are great.
Come in.
Master, Captain Sun,
may I ask a few questions?
You called Wu Da a deadbeat.
What did you mean?
After they divorced,
Wu Da would constantly
harass Xiaole at her place.
And he borrowed a lot of money
from Xiaole too.
Wu Da really
has no shame as a man.
Before the divorce,
he was always jealous of Xiaole.
And he hit her.
After the divorce, he clung to her
like a leech, pestering her endlessly.
You witnessed Wu Da hitting Wang Xiaole?
A few times.
But it wasn't severe.
They mostly argued.
I don't want this life any longer!
Go live it by yourself!
Useless!
Say that to me again!
Say it again!
Useless!
You...
Let go of me!
Say it to me again!
Useless! You are useless!
You are useless!
Coward!
All you can do is hit women!
Don't touch me!
How dare you!
Let go!
How dare you defy me!
How dare you!
Disappear!
You!
Let me go!
They argued a lot?
Yes.
Haven't you ever thought
about standing up for Wang Xiaole?
They made up quickly after every fight.
Besides, Xiaole chose Wu Da herself.
I can't and won't
make any decisions for her.
But I-I did end up
regretting it a bit later.
Why did I have to lend Wu Da the money
to buy that apartment?
Without that apartment, Xiaole...
This is yours, right?
Yes.
Did you save every single
condom wrapper?
They're proof of love
between Xiaole and me.
Not a single one was lost or missed?
This brand isn't common here.
How did you get them?
From overseas sites.
I have payment records. You can check.
Have you ever switched brands?
No.
Once I set my mind on something,
I stick to it.
Did anyone else know
about your collection habit?
How could I let
anyone else know about it?
Master,
if Niu Bosheng is telling the truth.
He never used
any other brand of contraceptive.
Then what about those wrappers
in the pine forest?
Given Niu Bosheng's personality,
even if he used a different brand,
he would have taken
the wrapper back to keep.
He wouldn't have left it at the scene.
Captain Leng, Ye.
Listen.
I investigated
at the community hospital.
Niu Bosheng's locker
was indeed broken into.
The clothes and bag really were stolen.
His colleagues at the community hospital
can confirm all this.
But since there's
no surveillance footage,
we can't rule out
that he staged it himself.
After all, the DNA evidence
points directly to him now.
But it's also true that Niu Bosheng
rented a place near Huang Chong's home
before the crime occurred.
If he really planned to commit murder,
there'd be no reason for him to do that.
Master,
don't you think we found
Niu Bosheng a little too easily?
If no third party knew
about his collecting habit,
then those wrappers in the pine forest
were planted there intentionally
to lead us straight to Niu Bosheng.
Also, if Niu Bosheng
is telling the truth,
that means Wu Da lied to us.
His relationship with Wang Xiaole
might not be as good as he claimed.
Officers, you're back again.
(Shancheng Community)
(If those condom wrappers
were planted intentionally,)
(then the real killer passing the gate)
(was likely intentional too.)
(He did it to lead us to the pond)
(and let us find
the critical clothing evidence.)
(So we'd incriminate Niu Bosheng.)
(He must have planned an exit strategy)
(before doing this.)
(An exit route hidden
from surveillance cameras.)
Everyone, gather round.
(Convenience Service Center)
We need all surveillance footage
around this community hospital.
Don't overlook any camera
that might've caught the bag thief.
Understood.
Six months.
It's nearly the maximum retention period
for public area surveillance.
Would he time the theft
right before the footage expired?
It's possible.
Niu Bosheng seems pretty twisted.
Maybe he did it himself.
Classic hypocrisy.
We still have to investigate.
Yes.
Move out. Spread the search.
Over there.
And there. Find more.
Got it.
You lent Wu Da that 200,000 yuan
for his apartment, right?
That money actually
came from Niu Bosheng.
Truth is, I wasn't particularly close
with Niu Bosheng.
He just approached me
out of the blue once,
asking me to lend the money
to Wu Da under my name.
Did Wu Da know about this?
He probably found out.
After he repaid the loan,
during a class reunion,
I got drunk
and spilled the truth.
Wu Da was sitting right
next to me at the time.
Logically, he should have heard it.
But I'm really not sure.
Sir.
Excuse me.
Is the surveillance camera yours?
Yes, it is.
What's up?
I'm from the police department.
I'd like to know if you keep
the footage from six months ago?
Yes.
Great! Where is it?
Over here.
Okay.
Niu Bosheng?
I remember him.
I fought with him back in school.
(Yunxi Police)
So it really was him?
So far,
the evidence directly points to him.
He's twisted.
Never thought after all these years,
he...
It's all my fault.
I didn't protect Xiaole.
Alright.
Calm down.
Tell us what you know about Niu Bosheng.
I don't know much either.
I think he works as a doctor
at a major hospital.
Do you know
that for your wedding apartment,
part of the money was loaned by him
under another classmate's name?
I don't know.
If I had known it was his money,
I wouldn't have taken it.
You are very familiar with the area
around Shancheng Community, right?
Have you been to that patch
of woods north of it?
I probably went there
when I was buying the house.
But not since then.
You know the Dongyuan Community?
That urban village, right?
Have you been there?
Before the divorce,
I bought groceries there.
Are you sure?
Then do you know
Niu Bosheng holds a weekly clinic
at the Dongyuan Community Hospital?
No, I didn't.
(Tuxi Express Supermarket)
Tired?
If you are tired, take a break.
That parcel pickup point owner
really went all out.
From 8 AM to 10 PM,
365 days a year,
he doesn't delete
a single bit of footage.
He gets a new one once it's full.
And it's all HD.
If other places
had surveillance like this,
how much easier our job would be.
These parcel pickup services
often deal with issues
like lost packages, damaged items,
items taken by mistake,
and even people stealing packages.
I guess they're sick of the hassle too.
They've been scared.
Hello?
Where are you?
Okay, I'm coming out right now.
Jing.
Bringing food for Lei?
Yes. Busy, huh?
I need to go.
What brings you here?
Bringing you food.
Porridge.
Nice!
Looks like you'll work late again.
Go eat it now.
I need to walk the little one.
Okay.
Take it slow on the way back.
Be careful.
Long and the others might be hungry.
I brought enough for all.
Head back now.
Bye.
- What's that?
- Coming.
Fuel is coming.
Let me see what's good?
Here, take two boxes.
One box is enough.
Just one box?
Ziwu.
Come on.
Jing really knows how to look after us.
Wouldn't let us go hungry.
You must have smelled it.
I was about to bring yours over.
Jing brought it.
Yeah.
Come on. Eat up and then back to work.
Tastes great.
Don't just eat.
Have some water.
I'll open it.
I'm leaving.
Lei.
What? Get in.
Is there any new discovery?
Nothing yet.
You should go eat too.
Call me if you find anything.
Okay.
Eat slowly.
(Tuxi Express Supermarket)
Captain Leng,
come here.
Look.
Wu Da?
Wu Da framed Niu Bosheng.
But during the time of the incident,
the dog-walking uncle clearly saw
Wu Da drinking in the flower bed.
Let's go.
Yes.
Still the same path every day.
Another one?
Young people
drink heavily.
(What's the injury on your hand?)
I forgot too.
Probably bumped into something.
Mao, let's go home.
Happy now?
How'd you get over here?
Come here.
Master.
♪Replacing the weight of tears
with that of sweat♪
♪Covering the gunshot's sound
with wounds♪
♪No one is born unyielding and strong♪
♪But because someone
always rushes ahead♪
♪To shield us from the storm♪
♪When every extraordinary act
becomes routine♪
♪Just to polish the badge
upon their shoulder♪
♪Like light surging unseen
through the night♪
♪Converging into your form♪
♪Looking up♪
♪Such dazzling glory♪
♪Like hope♪
♪Reaching out its arms♪
♪Cloaked in light♪
♪Alone, they charge ahead♪
♪Traversing♪
♪The battlefield of fate♪